<paragraph><Unknown>Boehner</Unknown> <Person>Obama</Person> psychic shield 
<Unknown>RealSexEdSavesLives</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> 
<Person>Amanda Ben Hyde</Person> <Unknown>UTD</Unknown> police 
steelers steelernation <Person>Obama</Person> 
roadrapers imonaboat 85degrees november globalwarming brudders itsnovember 
<Unknown>Holister</Unknown> models mall blackfriday hottie models shopping abs 
decemberwish <Unknown>BEROTOT</Unknown> 
<Location>New York</Location> <Location>usa</Location> timesquare april 2012 
brittanyybetch newyork <Person>ginny</Person> 329 rude red car 
police fivepointoh mustang 
webisodes police jaredbrady heavenkimchi 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Location>Jordans</Location> 
spolobsteashdash 79<Person>miles</Person> cancer movember 
mom <Location>cairo</Location> airpo back welcome home 
homosexuality sorrynotsorry notoffensive religion truth 
expresion a religion culture 
razor <Organization>NFL</Organization> <Organization>Gillette</Organization> 
thatshitcray crazy funny hurricanesandy <Person>brad</Person> 
<Organization>Sandy Terra Nova Scout Group</Organization> pccrovers 
<Location>Cairo</Location> 
aidsawareness jci jciphilippines <Unknown>STD</Unknown> <Person>HIV</Person> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> 
<Unknown>White</Unknown> <Person>Obama</Person> 
decemberwish 
<Person>Obama</Person> American Citizens <Unknown>NDAAruling</Unknown> tcot 
football gay gayboy gayboys gayguys gaylove gaymarriage freedom kissgay boyloveboy lgbt freelove emokiss gayrights 
beautiful lovo my dog white like android jj followme 
<Location>Brooklyn</Location> flooding hurricanesandy friends noheast <Unknown>Prayers</Unknown> 
<Organization>UEFA</Organization> <Unknown>Champions</Unknown> <Unknown>League</Unknown> <Person>ChampionsLeague</Person> <Unknown>FCBarcelona</Unknown> <Person>FCB Bara</Person> <Unknown>CampNou</Unknown> <Unknown>FCBMuseum</Unknown> <Unknown>Messi</Unknown> 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Person>OBAMA</Person> President <Unknown>BLACK</Unknown> <Unknown>JET</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Drugs</Unknown> <Unknown>Buddha</Unknown> 
<Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> lolz youwish 
<Unknown>AugustWish</Unknown> <Unknown>SeptemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>OctoberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>NovemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>Happiness</Unknown> 
<Person><Unknown>Hurricane</Unknown> Sandy</Person> hotelcafe rockdrive friends help hurricanesandy 
<Unknown>Payaaye</Unknown> hardy blackfriday pearls shopping nomess hollahz pagnit iwassnoringtoo ohwell 
<Person>OBAMA</Person> <Unknown>LMFAO</Unknown> <Unknown>Thug</Unknown> 
<Unknown>SternShowComiX</Unknown> <Person>Howard AGT Round</Person> <Unknown>MFBrooklyn</Unknown> <Unknown>HOWARDSTERN</Unknown> <Unknown>STERNSHOWCOMIX</Unknown> zenabuddysgirl southernjew 
<Unknown>Religion</Unknown> <Unknown>Relationship</Unknown> 
<Unknown>AFetusIsAHuman</Unknown> antiaboion <Unknown>Abolionist</Unknown> aboion <Unknown>Fetus</Unknown> <Unknown>AbolishHumanAboion</Unknown> babies <Unknown>EndAboion</Unknown> <Unknown>Love</Unknown> <Unknown>ChildrenAreABlessing</Unknown> <Unknown>Miracles</Unknown> <Unknown>ProLife</Unknown> <Unknown>StopAboion</Unknown> <Unknown>SpeakLife</Unknown> <Unknown>SaveOurBabies</Unknown> <Unknown>NationalRightToLife</Unknown> latinobaby latinababy 40daysforlifeLR 40daysforlife <Unknown>BlackGenocide</Unknown> blackbaby whitebabies whiteWomen <Unknown>LatinaWomen</Unknown> <Unknown>ArkansasRightToLife</Unknown> 
pitbull <Location>Montreal</Location> 11 59 globalwarming 
blackfriday occupy ola tents 
<Unknown>Da</Unknown> <Unknown>Accessories</Unknown> <Unknown>MercedesVision</Unknown> <Unknown>Religion</Unknown> <Unknown>Fendi</Unknown> <Unknown>LVblanket</Unknown> <Unknown>SF</Unknown>49ers <Unknown>HallOfFame</Unknown> S550 <Unknown>Blessed</Unknown> 
<Unknown>ElenaGornall</Unknown>1 <Unknown>EmilyStua</Unknown> X caitmurphy <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Shibuya</Unknown> <Location>japan</Location> <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> hiv aids instadaily instapic 
<Organization>Argos</Organization> <Unknown>Grey</Unknown> <Unknown>Cup</Unknown> 2012 
tamore 1mother 
thrift store 50 blackfriday 
auntie newyork babyshower cousin lovethem pay stophashtagging 
newyork brooklinbridge nightime 
<Person>AGT</Person> performance 
championsleague zenith win 
<Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> 
<Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> 
gay gayboy gayboys gayguys gaylove gayrights gaymarriage love lgbt kissgay boyloveboy freedom freelove 
<Person>Harry Christmas</Person> twitcam 2010 
<Unknown>Movember</Unknown> <Unknown>Mustache</Unknown> November cancer donations 
lacaafaiR <Person>Jay</Person> z <Person>Obama</Person> 
November 27th <Location>Tahrir Square</Location> November 27th <Unknown>TIME</Unknown> <Person>Bobby Ghosh</Person> ghoshworld 
pizza vodka food foodporn goodness grandma angelinas newyorkpizza 
gays <Location>America</Location> truth interesting aboion 
<Location>Liverpool</Location> <Organization>Aids</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Schoolhouse</Unknown> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Movie</Unknown> <Location>Central SCHOOLHOUSE</Location> <Location>ROCK</Location> <Unknown>ELECTION</Unknown> <Unknown>COLLECTION</Unknown> <Unknown>Schoolhouse</Unknown> <Location>Rock</Location> The <Unknown>Preamble</Unknown> September 23, 2008 
galatasaray championsleague 
<Unknown>DIVA</Unknown> dayofthediva <Organization>Eagle Manchester</Organization> <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> katherineellis1 
<Person>BlackFriday</Person> shopping spree 1<Unknown>DWorldMerch</Unknown> onedirection 
lukebullock <Person>OBama</Person> 
Daisy jerk store 
<Unknown>AHH</Unknown> winter mornings <Unknown>Decemberwish</Unknown> 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>KevinHa</Unknown> <Unknown>RP</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Cyber</Unknown> Monday purchase <Organization>Police Box</Organization> leggings <Unknown>Tardis</Unknown> leggings blackmilkclothing awesomeness 
vaneycj aids 
<Person>Obama</Person> 
todayshow yolo globalwarming rocking morning night 
<Unknown>Alinin</Unknown> telefonundan galatasaray championsleague cimbom cimbombom ultraaslan instagram 
<Unknown>Horse</Unknown> shoes jeans true 
bird seaguls malibu november globalwarming 
ocean acidification WA <Location>Seattle</Location> tvnews globalwarming photographers 
allietotheb band aids silver radness 
human history skeptical religion 
nofilter <Unknown>Browns</Unknown> <Organization>NFL Cleveland</Organization> <Unknown>GoBrowns</Unknown> 
<Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Bihday</Unknown> <Unknown>TqALLAH</Unknown> <Unknown>LoveISLAM</Unknown> <Unknown>LoveUallLillahiTaala</Unknown> 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>WhoDat</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Dank</Unknown> <Person><Unknown>Funksticks</Unknown> sandy</Person> benefit 
Election night 
<Unknown>Mohamed</Unknown> <Unknown>Mahmoud</Unknown> 2012 protest police riot revolution tahrir clashes <Location>cairo</Location> <Location>egypt</Location> egyptian me usefsalah ua07 march acab anarchy youth photography photographer photooftheday picoftheday instagram instacanvas teargas graffiti strong soldiers filmmaker cinema followme chants 
uniform <Organization>NFL</Organization> 
<Location>bahrain</Location> 
<Unknown>NOM</Unknown> DE LA <Unknown>MARQUE</Unknown> <Unknown>TAILLE</Unknown> <Unknown>EMAIL</Unknown> 
grandma sweetest lady cancer 
religions people 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>Bush</Unknown> tcot sgp teapay <Person>JEZEBEL</Person> 
theater visual aids 
newyork 
<Location>Cotton</Location> <Person>Candy Cairo</Person> 
<Person>RIP Young</Person> Prince young homie cancer <Unknown>CureFIP</Unknown> 
<Organization>Philippine Crame Church</Organization> police 
cancer event alexthao terryhe shimmycocopuffsss 
twitter aboion 
<Person>Pandora</Person> election season <Person>Obama</Person> 
 lavishemporium boutique blackfriday blackfridaysale blackfriday2012 thanksgiving thanksgivingsale cybermonday armcandy accessories brazilianhair curlyhair handbags idohair isellhair indianhair jewelry kinkyhair laceclosures malaysianhair order peruvianhair quality sale shoes straighthair virginhair virginextensions wavyhair 
<Unknown>Dogs</Unknown> <Unknown>Cute</Unknown> <Unknown>MobCam</Unknown> <Unknown>InstaDogs</Unknown> <Unknown>InstaAnimals</Unknown> <Person>Adorable Pets</Person> <Unknown>FoundAndLost</Unknown> 
<Organization>Post</Organization> election rice suculentBCN 
newyork 
backyard bar parkslope <Location>brooklyn</Location> newyork brunch egg yolk yum food foodporn 
<Unknown>Finna</Unknown> <Unknown>Raising</Unknown> <Unknown>Canes</Unknown> starving vbf1 blackfriday shopping leftovers text versagram versalove 
Work flowww bakers blackfriday death 
movie <Unknown>RealHughJackman</Unknown> decemberwish bihday gift 
<Location>Japan</Location> election remote vote 
fuckoff <Person>Zimmerman</Person> deserve life photo staged lame killer poor trayvon 
 
<Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> 
gayboy gayboys gayguys gaymarriage gayrights freedom freelove street lgbt love onedirection harrystyles luoisthomilison 
<Organization>Teenage Cancer Trust</Organization> 2nd year professorgreen 
frsharabianluv subway nyc newyork <Organization>Subway</Organization> stories vol.1 zlbg 
<Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Dvdrip</Unknown> movie download <Unknown>Actors</Unknown> <Unknown>Eihi</Unknown> <Unknown>Shiina</Unknown> <Unknown>Cay</Unknown> <Person>Izumi Mame</Person> <Unknown>Yamada</Unknown> <Unknown>Yukihide</Unknown> <Person>Benny Ikuko Sawada</Person> <Unknown>Itsuji</Unknown> <Unknown>Itao</Unknown> <Unknown>Akane</Unknown> <Unknown>Akanezawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Ayano</Unknown> <Unknown>Yamamoto</Unknown> <Unknown>Jiji</Unknown> <Unknown>Tsugumi</Unknown> <Unknown>Nagasawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Download</Unknown> <Unknown>Bloody</Unknown> good <Organization>New York Post</Organization> <Unknown>Strap</Unknown> April <Unknown>Eihi</Unknown> <Unknown>Shiina</Unknown> <Unknown>Itsuji</Unknown> <Unknown>Itao</Unknown> <Unknown>Keyman</Unknown> <Unknown>Yukihide</Unknown> <Person>Benny Tokyo</Person> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Chief</Unknown> <Unknown>Jiji</Unknown> <Unknown>Barabara</Unknown> <Unknown>Man</Unknown> <Person>Ikuko Sawada</Person> <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Wikipedia</Unknown> Japanese American <Unknown>Yoshihiro</Unknown> <Unknown>Nishimura</Unknown> <Unknown>Wikipedia</Unknown> <Unknown>Rotten</Unknown> <Unknown>Tomatoes</Unknown> <Unknown>Review</Unknown> <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Organization>Netflix Tokyo</Organization> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> 
<Unknown>WesleySafadao</Unknown> <Unknown>GarotaSafada</Unknown> app android 
 150 prostate cancer <Person>Ronald McDonald</Person> 
kylegibbons jelluhfish aids 
<Unknown>HurricaneSandy</Unknown> donations <Unknown>UConnCountry</Unknown> <Unknown>BleedBlue</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Lsb</Unknown> love lsb girllovegirl gay gayboy gayguys gaylove gayrights gaymarriage freedom freelove love lgbt 
airpo police 
movember <Unknown>Day</Unknown> 16 cancer 
election day <Unknown>Doad</Unknown> <Person>Obama</Person> blue parka 
<Unknown>Mexes</Unknown> <Unknown>Chilena</Unknown> <Unknown>Francia</Unknown> <Person>Italia</Person> <Location>Venezuela</Location> <Person>UCL ChampionsLeague</Person> <Unknown>Calcio</Unknown> <Unknown>Futbol</Unknown> <Unknown>ACMilan</Unknown> <Unknown>Golazo</Unknown> <Unknown>Gol</Unknown> <Unknown>ForzaMilan</Unknown> <Unknown>Rossonero</Unknown> 
Love religion 
<Unknown>Hunting</Unknown> <Unknown>Trophy</Unknown> varMITT exposeLiberal co2hog P2 tcot teapay gop <Unknown>DEMS</Unknown> <Unknown>LIBERAL</Unknown> 
memoriesIwontforget 
money <Organization>Teenage Cancer Trust</Organization> 
<Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> square <Location>egypt</Location> tahrir <Location>cairo</Location> revolution ihatemuslimbrotherhood freedom freeegypt instagram instalife 
Amen spawnio20 <Location>City</Location> <Person>CL ChampionsLeague</Person> 
<Unknown>Equality</Unknown> breakfast gay gayboy gayboys gayguys gaylove gayrights gaymarriage kissgay freelove freedom lgbt 
<Person>Micky</Person> mouse <Unknown>NewYork</Unknown> newyorkcity <Person>NYC TimeSquare</Person> selfie city <Person>micky</Person> mickymouse 
daddy <Person>BlackFriday</Person> shopping golf 
kaka thebest bernabeu championsleague realmadrid 
<Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> <Location>Cairo</Location> egipto 
<Unknown>Hea</Unknown> <Unknown>Smile</Unknown> kinggoldchains tyga kingcairo <Unknown>SoSweet</Unknown> <Unknown>Tyga</Unknown> <Location>Cairo</Location> King Studio <Unknown>Family</Unknown> <Unknown>Love</Unknown> <Unknown>Baby</Unknown> <Unknown>LastKings</Unknown> <Unknown>Kingin</Unknown> <Unknown>HardWork</Unknown> <Unknown>Small</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> 
breast cancer helmets 
<Unknown>Barbeon</Unknown> police old lady parking lot <Unknown>KMa</Unknown> police <Unknown>SUV</Unknown> crusier drugs guns ticket taxdollarsatwork 
Global warming <Location>Baltimore</Location> <Unknown>GlobalWarming</Unknown> 
<Person>LLS Sandy Little</Person> <Unknown>Cheeks</Unknown> 
aboion clinic oxymoronic 
Ghost corner <Location>Cairo</Location> <Location>Illinois</Location> 
<Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> <Unknown>VOTE</Unknown> 
<Unknown>CountryStrong</Unknown> Travis cutie cancer favorite 
game nfl nyg gmen football sunday funday 
cristians muslims religion church mosk extremist terrorist 911 wtc binladen osama osamabinladen alqaeda alqaida <Person>al</Person> kaida mudjahedin taliban revolution ignorence nonesense 
<Unknown>Red</Unknown> <Unknown>White</Unknown> <Unknown>Blue</Unknown> Christmas Tree re election President <Person>Barack Obama</Person> 
bigtiggershow Big <Unknown>Bro</Unknown> <Unknown>Gmail</Unknown> <Person>HIV</Person> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Awareness</Unknown> <Unknown>Record</Unknown> <Unknown>Interview</Unknown> 
little adventure <Location>Rome</Location> <Unknown>Newyork</Unknown> 
 
I love you <Person>Henry</Person> hate cancer 
<Unknown>New</Unknown> <Person>Zimmerman</Person> <Unknown>Dj</Unknown> <Unknown>Clue</Unknown> voice <Unknown>Trayvon</Unknown> toast 
religion atheism 
<Unknown>Hryda</Unknown> onmyPboishit thuglifer <Person>Blackfriday</Person> imblackeveryday blacksheep backonmyfeet stillupstillaintwent2sleep <Unknown>Jumma</Unknown> prayerday <Person>Rip</Person> V12<Unknown>BmR</Unknown> 
Same Sex <Unknown>Marriage</Unknown> <Unknown>Shi</Unknown> gaymarriage equality fckh8 gay lesbian <Unknown>LGBT</Unknown> 
best grandmother <Person>Bibi BlackFriday</Person> <Unknown>Love</Unknown> Amazing 
Dixie gurdwara textbook world religion class uoft 
Pay hard police pay 
tbt Halloween weathermen hurricaneSandy 
 
hands up budha religion incense techno song memories 
best night 
<Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> Less stress Less pain Less problems Less tears More happiness More laugh More love 
<Person>GEORGE ZIMMERMAN</Person> <Unknown>JUSTICE</Unknown> 
little man rocking <Unknown>Burberry</Unknown> <Unknown>True</Unknown> <Unknown>Religion</Unknown> Olympics 
<Unknown>Boo</Unknown> football nfl cfl football qualitytime putaringonit 
<Person>African</Person> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> 
architecture postsandy hurricanesandy nj 
 <Unknown>PhonseeMac</Unknown> <Unknown>HeyBoo</Unknown> <Unknown>YouLoveShauna</Unknown> cancer 
justinbieber <Person>Obama</Person> 
<Unknown>Decemberwish</Unknown> december ig igers igdaily photodaily mymonth hashtags nofilter tweegram instagood instagram instamood instalikes instaphoto instafamous instafollow followforfollow likesforlikes f4f l4l 10likes smile happy 
gas problem in <Person><Person>NYC</Person> sandy</Person> ny nyc 
bitches repost <Person>dat</Person> nigga mase <Unknown>Magic</Unknown> <Person>Johnson HIV Aids</Person> <Unknown>OhBabyiLikeItRaw</Unknown> 
good joke fantasy aboion flop nfl fantasyfootball 
<Unknown>Snacks</Unknown> to eat pinkelly oreos hurricanesandy 
<Unknown>Ur</Unknown> <Unknown>Funny</Unknown> <Organization>Football</Organization> <Unknown>CyberGift</Unknown> Troops <Person>ISS Seahawks</Person> myCancer <Unknown>Journey</Unknown> 
tree snow ig igers instagram fallentree hurricanesandy <Person>sandy</Person> winter autumn seasons jj photooftheday likeforlike picoftheday leaves cold 
9 months One <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>TrayvonMain</Unknown> 
 
collection hellokitty newyork shotglass 
Bad religion 
<Unknown>FashionablyDelicious</Unknown> oakville cancer fundraiser 
<Person>BlackFriday</Person> purchases 2am sephora freshfounder lushvalleyfair julepmaven 
<Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>Kingcairo</Unknown> 
One Direction <Unknown>Congrats</Unknown> One Direction <Unknown>Ovarian</Unknown> <Unknown>Cancer</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Rocking</Unknown> 99 problems <Person>Obama</Person> 
<Location>PARIS</Location> <Unknown>SAINT</Unknown> <Person>GERMAIN PSG PSGPOO</Person> C1 <Person>Championsleague</Person> <Unknown>Win</Unknown> <Location>Paris</Location> 
election predictions 
<Organization>AIDS Project Los Angeles</Organization> <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> <Unknown>FoodDrive</Unknown> 
breast cancer awareness soccer game vsyulee november27th bethere shootout prizes 530 720 wearpink 
<Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> square Today 27November2012 protest revolution <Location>Tahrir Square</Location> <Location>Cairo</Location> <Location>Egypt</Location> tahrirsquare brutal police force teargas gas 
<Unknown>PRESIDENT</Unknown> <Unknown>AT</Unknown> <Unknown>STARBUCKS</Unknown> 
cancer karemcitac pabloacap 
First Lady firstlady obama michelleobama merica <Location>usa</Location> 
pregnant aboion decent <Unknown>GTFOH</Unknown> <Unknown>TheThirst</Unknown> 
growing up <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> <Unknown>Graduation</Unknown>2011 unibocconi 
read tonight <Unknown>AudacityOfHope</Unknown> <Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>BarackObama</Unknown> <Unknown>ProudDad</Unknown> 
decemberwish <Unknown>Oppa</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Souls</Unknown> up spirit is back good old days tahrir <Location>egypt</Location> <Location>cairo</Location> travel 
anti <Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>FB</Unknown> page cousins <Person>Joe Di</Person> 
<Unknown>Rap</Unknown> And <Unknown>Religion</Unknown> book release pay The Diplomat 
revenge antagonise football fans 
<Organization>Football Skills Clinic</Organization> 
<Unknown>GoT</Unknown> Cast <Unknown>Game</Unknown> of <Unknown>Thrones</Unknown> 
telltalegames holy smokes telltale <Unknown>Game</Unknown> of thrones 
<Unknown>SarahSarah</Unknown>256 <Unknown>WinceyWillis</Unknown>1 <Location>India</Location> mega millionaires animals 
dallxscxm <Unknown>YourBoyMyles</Unknown> animals 
<Unknown>InnovativeHindu</Unknown> ndtv <Unknown>Headlinestoday</Unknown> <Unknown>Muslim</Unknown> <Unknown>Org</Unknown> <Person>PFI Hindu</Person> <Location>Temple</Location> <Location>Calicut</Location> <Unknown>Kozhikode</Unknown> Sunday 
Football Season 
<Unknown>RyanBrownWJOX</Unknown> <Person><Unknown>JayHopeIsHere</Unknown> Joey</Person>35209 <Unknown>UAB</Unknown> football program 
<Unknown>JeffSolochek</Unknown> <Location>Florida</Location> superintendents school board members testing concerns recommendations <Unknown>ErikaDonalds</Unknown> edFL 
<Organization>SteveStfler EDUCATION</Organization> <Unknown>SYSTEM</Unknown> 
<Unknown>SDLPlive</Unknown> gerardmcd93 <Organization>SDLP</Organization> povey living wage <Location>belfast</Location> mid <Unknown>Ulster</Unknown> council <Unknown>Mencap</Unknown> <Unknown>NI</Unknown> 
<Unknown>AnishNation</Unknown> <Unknown>Job</Unknown> oppounity Education <Unknown>Development</Unknown> <Unknown>Officer</Unknown> <Unknown>Nipissing</Unknown> <Unknown>Campus</Unknown> sharethis 
<Person>Robby Ratan</Person> avatars education <Unknown>MSUComASci</Unknown> <Unknown>MSU</Unknown> <Unknown>ITL</Unknown> 
<Unknown>NYSenate</Unknown> <Organization>New</Organization> Yorkers <Unknown>NYGovCuomo</Unknown> education agenda legislator 
<Unknown>Sale</Unknown> <Person>Allen Edmonds</Person> <Unknown>GRIDIRON</Unknown> <Unknown>Oxfords</Unknown> <Person>Brown Football</Person> <Location>Grain</Location> <Unknown>Leather</Unknown> 
<Unknown>StPetePD</Unknown> animalcruelty animals 
<Unknown>Game</Unknown> of <Unknown>Thrones</Unknown> 1.99 <Unknown>GameOfThrones</Unknown> <Unknown>GRRMspeaking</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Photos</Unknown> Of <Unknown>Bollywood</Unknown> <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> 
<Unknown>JeanneBaram</Unknown> <Person>Iain Duncan Smith</Person> food bank charity bankers povey 
zepvv international football 
allthelovelouis <Person>harry</Person> <Person>louis</Person> football game 
90sfootball <Person>James Richardson Italian</Person> cafe <Organization>Football</Organization> <Person><Person>Italia</Person> 
angela</Person> std Animals <Unknown>ApoyoLeyAnimal</Unknown>087 
<Unknown>EssexFBU</Unknown> <Unknown>Brigade</Unknown> <Unknown>FBU</Unknown> education course <Unknown>WoleyHall</Unknown> <Unknown>EssexFBU</Unknown> <Unknown>NotGoingAway</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Baylor</Unknown> football <Location>Texas</Location> 
<Unknown>Daily</Unknown> <Unknown>Bread</Unknown> povey hunger <Unknown>WhyWePray</Unknown> 
Education money ignorance 
<Organization>University of Saskatchewan</Organization> students tuition fees free education 
rightsnet <Person>Iain Duncan Smith</Person> food bank charity <Unknown>TrussellTrust</Unknown> 
<Unknown>ORGY</Unknown> <Unknown>PORGY</Unknown> <Unknown>European</Unknown> <Unknown>Invasion</Unknown> <Person>DNA Origins</Person> Of <Unknown>Modern</Unknown> Europeans <Unknown>IFLScience</Unknown> 
ndtv <Location>Japan</Location> technology transfer pacts <Organization>Reserve Bank of India</Organization> 
<Organization>MindyRosier Public Education</Organization> <Unknown>Warriors</Unknown> <Unknown>Unite</Unknown> <Unknown>AllKidsNeedht</Unknown> quadgurl <Unknown>CMZR</Unknown> <Unknown>RodneyJordan</Unknown>4 <Unknown>TruthinTeaching</Unknown> teachin1100 
philo quotes education proper training nursery <Person>Plato</Person> 
ndtv <Unknown>NationalAwards</Unknown> <Unknown>Priyanka</Unknown> <Unknown>Chopra</Unknown> small town girl <Unknown>Kangana</Unknown> <Unknown>Ranaut</Unknown> 
Domestic violence womans financial dependence man woman education livelihood 
<Unknown>Man</Unknown> <Unknown>Ki</Unknown> <Unknown>Baat</Unknown> Prime Minister <Unknown>Narendra</Unknown> <Unknown>Modi</Unknown> All <Organization>India Radio</Organization> <Unknown>News</Unknown> 
outlawvern <Unknown>SHE</Unknown> <Person>S GOTTA</Person> <Unknown>HAVE</Unknown> IT HOLLYWOOD <Unknown>SHUFFLE</Unknown> smash 
<Location>Hollywood</Location> dneedles12 live repo LA tonight <Unknown>WISN</Unknown>12<Unknown>News</Unknown> <Unknown>Badgers</Unknown> <Unknown>Sweet</Unknown>16 
<Unknown>Okies</Unknown>4<Person>Carrie Carrie Underwood</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Bowl</Unknown> <Unknown>Surprise</Unknown> <Unknown>Guest</Unknown> <Person>Mr. Randy Travis</Person> 
<Unknown>NBCLA</Unknown> <Unknown>WillFerrell</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Fame</Unknown> star 
<Unknown>RevRichardColes</Unknown> <Person>Paul Hollywood</Person> mille feuilles 
<Organization>Hollywood Star Interview Magazine</Organization> January 1995 <Person>Julia Robes</Person> <Person>Tim Robbins</Person> <Person>Laurence Fishburne</Person> <Unknown>BestSeller</Unknown> <Organization>eBay</Organization> 
A List celebrity <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> iPhone 
<Unknown>BrooksBeau</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> weed 
<Person>Mr. Hollywood</Person> Mega <Unknown>Deal</Unknown> Thursday, March 26 gluten 
<Unknown>JBCrewdotcom</Unknown> <Person>Justin Bieber</Person> <Location>West Hollywood</Location> CA 
dollllllfaceee <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> 
<Unknown>TheAegiMaster</Unknown> <Unknown>Harlem</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Person>Jackson Mississippi</Person> 
<Unknown>Singer</Unknown> <Unknown>Actress</Unknown> <Unknown>MileyCyrus</Unknown> <Person>CD Jul</Person> 2008 <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Deals</Unknown> <Unknown>Bargains</Unknown> 
Lady9<Unknown>NewOrleans</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> history black men womanly roles 
<Unknown>Iam</Unknown>1izzo <Unknown>LeoDiCaprio</Unknown> young R B celebrities <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>YoungHollywood</Unknown> <Unknown>NextUp</Unknown> <Unknown>Movies</Unknown> etnow <Unknown>TM</Unknown> 
<Unknown>DuncanWhitehead</Unknown> whodunnit mystery books of the decade <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Times</Unknown> kindleespaol kindleunlimited kindle 
<Person>jesu Young</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> celebrity focused <Organization>Apple TV Apple TV</Organization> paulz 
Big12<Unknown>SposESPN</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> dneedles12 live repo LA tonight <Unknown>WISN</Unknown>12<Unknown>News</Unknown> <Unknown>Badgers</Unknown> 
<Person>jesu Young</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> celebrity focused <Organization>Apple TV Apple TV</Organization> paulz 
<Unknown>JOPDreke</Unknown> Secret Behind <Person>Liam Hollywood</Person> <Unknown>Celebs</Unknown> <Unknown>Explosive</Unknown> <Unknown>Muscle</Unknown> Gains 
<Location>HOLLYWOOD</Location> <Unknown>COLLAGE</Unknown> <Unknown>POSTER</Unknown> <Unknown>NICE</Unknown> <Unknown>AWORK</Unknown> 
<Unknown>JColeNC</Unknown> <Location>Forest Hills</Location> <Location>Hollywood</Location> Big <Person>Sean</Person> <Unknown>YG</Unknown>. <Unknown>Jeremih</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Queens</Unknown> Of The <Location>Stone</Location> <Unknown>Age</Unknown> seguira <Unknown>Cranberries</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> 
teresaamejiaa <Person>Kim K Hollywood</Person> 
<Person>B List</Person> celebrity <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> iPhone 
<Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Free</Unknown> Games <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> <Unknown>Game</Unknown> 
<Unknown>NerdPowersUnite</Unknown> Lady9<Unknown>NewOrleans</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> history emasculating black men 
E List celebrity <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> iPhone 
First millions <Organization>Hollywood Film TV</Organization> music moguls 
ayeeitsbeccaa <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> 
dollfacetrece <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> 
hamilt4 <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> 
<Unknown>Indiegogo</Unknown> kickstaer <Location>Hollywood</Location> movie trailer growthhacker 
<Unknown>Movie</Unknown> <Unknown>Finance</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>TOMOOffMarket</Unknown> 
<Unknown>VanityFair</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Bihday</Unknown> <Person>Steve McQueen</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> Cool 
<Unknown>Iam</Unknown>1izzo Big S O 2 <Unknown>LeoDiCaprio</Unknown> young R B celebrities <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>YoungHollywood</Unknown> <Unknown>NextUp</Unknown> <Unknown>Movies</Unknown> etnow <Unknown>TM</Unknown> 
<Unknown>TheAVClub</Unknown> <Unknown>ComedyCentral</Unknown> new series <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Location>FL</Location> 
A <Unknown>Deco</Unknown> <Unknown>Old</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Affair</Unknown> Wedding <Unknown>Decor</Unknown> pheasant feathers 
<Unknown>ArkansasAuthors</Unknown> <Unknown>AceCollins</Unknown> author Man s Best <Person>Hero Hollywood</Person> Lost 
<Location>Highway</Location> to <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Trailer</Unknown> <Unknown>YouTube</Unknown> 
<Organization>GOPLdrBrianKolb Hollywood Film TV</Organization> millions music moguls 
<Unknown>ATTI</Unknown> <Unknown>ML</Unknown>04orange <Person><Unknown>Bus</Unknown> Sam</Person> s Club <Organization>Orange</Organization> <Location>South Stopis</Location> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Domain</Unknown> <Unknown>Apts</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Monatana</Unknown> <Unknown>Ave</Unknown> <Unknown>Main</Unknown> <Unknown>St</Unknown> <Unknown>Beauticate</Unknown> <Unknown>SantaMonica</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> cool beachy cousin 
<Unknown>YouTube</Unknown> video kiss network <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Person><Unknown>Traincase</Unknown> LOLA</Person> V 
<Location>HOLLYWOOD</Location> <Unknown>THEATER</Unknown> <Person>ROW Hollywood</Person> <Location>East Hollywood</Location> <Organization>Chamber of Commerce</Organization> 
<Unknown>TheAVClub</Unknown> <Unknown>ComedyCentral</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Location>FL</Location> 
 <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> <Unknown>Applebees</Unknown> <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Nature</Unknown> <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> 
archeteer <Person>vic Pascual</Person> photography architecture <Location>Santiago</Location> <Location>Calatrava City</Location> of <Unknown>Arts</Unknown> and Sciences <Location>Valencia</Location> <Location>Spain</Location> 
<Person>Photography</Person> books <Unknown>Understanding</Unknown> <Unknown>Exposure</Unknown> itslikereally 
<Unknown>AUTOUPDATED</Unknown> <Unknown>Blogger</Unknown> blogs 
 <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> <Unknown>Applebees</Unknown> <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Nature</Unknown> <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> 
Top <Unknown>Secret</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Tutorials</Unknown> <Unknown>Trick</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> Special Effects 
monicatakvam <Unknown>Renaissance</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Prize</Unknown> 2015 <Unknown>RPP</Unknown>2015 
About <Organization>Page Establishing Trust</Organization> photography advice 
<Unknown>Network</Unknown> <Unknown>Easy</Unknown> <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Qualasha</Unknown> mikeshoys landscapes 
Life photography negatives develop 
<Unknown>ExclusiveTailor</Unknown> <Person>K Photography</Person> 
<Unknown>CutPics</Unknown> <Unknown>Microscopic</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> 
product all nighter sunrise neighbouring roof <Location>Leicester</Location> photography 
<Location>UK</Location> <Location>Highland</Location> <Person>Photography</Person> latest review produ yotpo 
<Unknown>DWAWest</Unknown> <Unknown>Monochrome</Unknown> adventures 120 picoftheday <Location>Newhaven</Location> <Location>Sussex</Location> photography landscape blackandwhite <Organization>Leica</Organization> 
<Person>Susanne</Person> white backdrop <Person>Carl Hult</Person> <Unknown>YouPic</Unknown> photography <Unknown>PIcSher</Unknown> <Unknown>TeamCanon</Unknown> 
<Unknown>GORILLA</Unknown> <Unknown>MONSOON</Unknown> <Unknown>LIVE</Unknown> <Unknown>XIII</Unknown> <Person>PHOTOGRAPHY</Person> 
love candy photography ellahaus wedding candybar vancouverwedding 
<Person><Unknown>OnePerfectShot</Unknown> LAWRENCE</Person> OF <Unknown>ARABIA</Unknown> Director of <Person>Photography</Person> <Person>Freddie Young</Person> Director <Person>David Lean</Person> 
<Unknown>AnnieLyden</Unknown> <Location>Barnes</Location> V and A <Person>S African</Person> photo tomorrow <Unknown>NatGalleriesSco</Unknown> <Unknown>NGSPonteCity</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Springtime</Unknown> Fly 
Director of <Person>Photography</Person> <Person>Bryan Pereira</Person> <Organization>Scarborough Photographic Club Ontario</Organization> 
mainlygems photography student ass hand cup 
high school choir photography idk 
ggwildlife225 <Unknown>WildLondoner</Unknown> <Unknown>WWTLondon</Unknown> <Location>London</Location> <Unknown>Wildlife</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> 
<Unknown>MatHombauer</Unknown> conce photography flickr group 
book photoshoot nigga mean Active <Person>Photography</Person> 
<Unknown>RFWPPI</Unknown> 2015 wedding porait photography conference 
Growth Of <Unknown>Video</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Business</Unknown> <Unknown>Fstoppers</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Awesome</Unknown> Examples Of <Unknown>Fashion</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> 
<Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Market</Unknown> 
<Unknown>DWAWest</Unknown> <Unknown>Monochrome</Unknown> adventures picoftheday <Location>Newhaven</Location> <Location>Sussex</Location> photography landscape blackandwhite <Organization>Leica</Organization> 
<Unknown>RFWPPI</Unknown> 2015 wedding and porait photography conference 
photography 
P41 <Unknown>Eisbrecher</Unknown> Director of <Person>Photography</Person> 
jasonburrows <Unknown>Landscape</Unknown> <Location>Loon Island</Location> <Unknown>Lighthouse</Unknown> miketaylorphoto 
photography photoofthed 
master flower photography <Unknown>Mother</Unknown> <Unknown>Nature</Unknown> <Unknown>Network</Unknown> 
Viewpoint and <Unknown>Angles</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> 
photography 
Last night photo shoot. 
kapchur photography natural canon freelance photos videography 
 <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> <Unknown>Applebees</Unknown> <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown> <Person>Photography</Person> <Unknown>Nature</Unknown> <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> 
<Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> CT <Unknown>EHchat</Unknown> 
<Unknown>WalesAirForum</Unknown> <Person>Roger Lewis Cardiff</Person> <Unknown>Airpochairman</Unknown> <Location>Cardiff</Location> <Location>Wales</Location> avgeek <Unknown>WalestotheWorld</Unknown> 
tibettruth travel trueTibet tourism erosion <Unknown>Tibetan</Unknown> culture 
tibettruth trueTibet sacred landscape tourist theme park <Location>China</Location> terrorist regime travel tourism 
<Unknown>Astronomical</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> 
tibettruth trueTibet tourist theme park <Location>China</Location> terrorist regime travel tourism 
<Organization>CatalanMuseums Catalan Museum</Organization> tourism 
<Unknown>Traveller</Unknown>24 SA <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown> <Unknown>EHchat</Unknown> 
hany2m tourism <Location>Egypt</Location> <Unknown>CAPMAS</Unknown> 
tour Skills <Unknown>Development</Unknown> <Unknown>Programme</Unknown> <Unknown>Wakkerstroom</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Turismo</Unknown> <Unknown>Zaia</Unknown> <Unknown>SmaGuide</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Unknown>Vinitaly</Unknown> 
<Unknown>WWFSouthAfrica</Unknown> <Unknown>Traveller</Unknown>24 SA <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> global sustainability <Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown> 
geckobike tourism <Location>Tibet</Location> 
<Location>Iran</Location> <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> <Location>Shiraz</Location> <Unknown>Hafezieh</Unknown> <Unknown>Nowruz</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Location>Iran</Location> <Unknown>MustSeeIran</Unknown> 
ijen <Unknown>Crater</Unknown> <Location>East Java</Location> <Location>Indonesia</Location> tourism eastjava holiday kids <Location>Indonesia</Location> 
<Location>Atlantic City</Location> tourism 
ac atlantic <Location>jersey</Location> 
<Person>HM RoyalMuseumJo</Person> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Person>Jordan ShareYourJordan</Person> <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown> <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown> <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> 
<Location>Manchester</Location> tourism sightseeing 
<Unknown>AnasAlShariff</Unknown> <Person>HM RoyalMuseumJo</Person> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Person>Jordan ShareYourJordan</Person> <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown> <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown> <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> 
tourism 
<Person>meta</Person> guide lc <Location>St. Lucia</Location> <Unknown>Record</Unknown> Breaking <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Unknown>Growth</Unknown> 
<Unknown>AnasAlShariff</Unknown> <Person>RoyalMuseumJo</Person> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> in <Location>Jordan</Location> <Person>ShareYourJordan</Person> <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown> <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown> <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> 
taxi driver <Unknown>Artane</Unknown> tourism 
<Location>United States</Location> 
th3programe <Location>United States</Location> 
njerudeee <Unknown>Security</Unknown> <Location>Kenya</Location> <Location>Tanzania</Location> tourism 
<Unknown>TOURISM</Unknown> <Unknown>WEBSITE</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Dmitris</Unknown> <Unknown>Tsoukalas</Unknown> iamanathenian private company tourism <Location>Athens</Location> <Location>Greece</Location> <Unknown>SoMeT</Unknown>15EU 
instanusantara challenge <Location>indonesia</Location> tourism world <Unknown>Gunung</Unknown> 
<Location>London</Location> Mayor <Person>Boris Johnson</Person> tourism <Location>London</Location> <Unknown>Evening</Unknown> <Unknown>Standard</Unknown> 
<Unknown>CCCU</Unknown> hospitality tourism logoideas kentchoices 
<Unknown>EstherPassaris</Unknown> <Organization>AMB</Organization> A <Person>Mohammed</Person> tourism sector 
Japanese hot spring <Unknown>Kurokawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Onsen</Unknown> <Location>Tokyo</Location> Olympics <Location>Japan</Location> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> Olympics 
th3programe <Location>United States</Location> 
masterclassing <Unknown>Digital</Unknown> <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Unknown>Masterclass</Unknown> <Location>Dubai</Location> April 15th 
<Location>North East</Location> tourism 
masterclassing <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Unknown>Brandwatch</Unknown> 
th3programe <Location>United States</Location> 
<Location>Iran</Location> <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> <Location>Shiraz</Location> <Unknown>Hafezieh</Unknown> <Unknown>Nowruz</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Location>Iran</Location> <Unknown>MustSeeIran</Unknown> 
<Organization>Post</Organization> <Location>Nigeria</Location> <Unknown>FG</Unknown> medical tourism hospitals <Organization>Post</Organization> <Location>Nigeria</Location> 
<Unknown>BittuSahgal</Unknown> <Location>Rwanda</Location> tourism <Location>India</Location> 
<Organization>Post</Organization> <Location>Nigeria</Location> <Unknown>FG</Unknown> medical tourism hospitals <Organization>Post</Organization> <Location>Nigeria</Location> <Unknown>WeTriumphStill</Unknown> <Unknown>IchooseGEJ</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Head</Unknown> of School <Organization>Hospitality Management</Organization> <Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> tourism <Location>Ireland</Location> 
oleebranch <Unknown>Kyaninga</Unknown> <Unknown>Triathlon</Unknown> The <Unknown>Mighty</Unknown> <Unknown>Rim</Unknown> <Unknown>UGblogs</Unknown> 256<Unknown>Blogs</Unknown> <Unknown>VisitUganda</Unknown> <Unknown>Triathlon</Unknown> <Unknown>Fitness</Unknown> <Unknown>Fitfam</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Humber</Unknown> <Location>East Liberal</Location> stelmanflynnMHA tourism guide 
<Unknown>Tourism</Unknown> <Location>Barcelona</Location> 
</paragraph>
