<paragraph><Unknown>Boehner</Unknown> attempts mind control but  <Person>Obama</Person> puts up a  psychic shield
 <Unknown>RealSexEdSavesLives</Unknown> Cool condoms for <Unknown>PPNC</Unknown>  39 s outreach in recognition of <Unknown>World</Unknown>  <Organization>AIDS</Organization> day
<Person>Amanda Ben</Person> and I at <Location>Hyde</Location> <Location><Location>UTD</Location></Location> city v police
 steelers  steelernation  obama
<Unknown>Day</Unknown> on the river  roadrapers  imonaboat  85degrees  itsnovember?  globalwarming  brudders
<Unknown>Holister</Unknown> models  holister  models  hottie  mall  blackfriday  shopping  abs 
 decemberwish <Unknown>BEROTOT</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Hey</Unknown> <Location>New York</Location> I miss u...  ny  newyork  <Location>new  york</Location>  <Location>usa</Location>  timesquare  april  2012
Me and @brittanyybetch being belligerent on the highway  roadtrip  rude  newyork  red  car @<Person>ginny</Person> 329
Was bound to happen sooner or later  police  fivepointoh  mustang
While shooting my new webisodes we just got stopped by undercover police.... Do we look suspicious to you? @jaredbrady @heavenkimchi
<Person>Obama</Person> rocks <Location>Jordans</Location> 
<Unknown>Lets</Unknown> do this  sportlobstertashdash  79<Person>miles</Person>  cancer  movember
She  39 s finally back  mom <Location>cairo</Location> airport backk welcome home
There ya go.  homosexuality  sorrynotsorry  notoffensive  religion  truth
<Person>arte</Person> es <Person>arte</Person> virgen se <Person>guadalupe</Person>  expresion  a religion culture
Why thank you for the free razor <Organization>NFL</Organization> <Organization>Gillette</Organization> 
 thatshitcray  crazy  funny  hurricanesandy  <Person>brad</Person>
<Person>Sandy</Person> checking out the 28th <Organization>Terra Nova Scout Group</Organization> meeting @pccrovers
A nice messy <Location>Cairo</Location>
<Unknown>Inspiring</Unknown> the <Unknown>Nation</Unknown>. <Unknown>STD</Unknown> <Person>HIV</Person> and <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Awareness</Unknown>  aids  aidsawareness  jci  jciphilippines
<Unknown>White</Unknown> <Person>Obama</Person>. 
 decemberwish
<Person>Obama</Person> is such a quot <Unknown>Nice</Unknown> Guy. quot Just look at how much he cares about American Citizens.  tcot  <Unknown>NDAAruling</Unknown> 
What it  39 s possible don  39 t like football?  gay  gayboy  gayboys  gayguys  gaylove  gaymarriage  freedom  kissgay  boyloveboy  lgbt  freelove  emokiss  gayrights
 beautiful  lovo  my  dog  white  like  android  jj  followme
<Location>Brooklyn</Location>  flooding  hurricanesandy <Unknown>Prayers</Unknown> for my family and friends in the northeast
The <Organization>UEFA</Organization> <Unknown>Champions</Unknown> <Unknown>League</Unknown>  39 s cup  <Organization>UEFA</Organization>  <Person>ChampionsLeague</Person>  <Unknown>FCBarcelona</Unknown>  <Person>FCB  Bara</Person>  <Unknown>CampNou</Unknown>  <Unknown>FCBMuseum</Unknown>  <Unknown>Messi</Unknown>
<Person>Obama</Person> for 4 more years  team  <Person>OBAMA</Person>  my  President  is  <Unknown>BLACK</Unknown>  <Unknown>JET</Unknown>
You know my religion. Drugs x <Unknown>Buddha</Unknown>
 <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> This as my bedroom wallpaper  lolz  youwish
<Unknown>AugustWish</Unknown> <Unknown>SeptemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>OctoberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>NovemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>FINALLY</Unknown> <Unknown>TYL</Unknown>  34  34  34  34  34  34 gt  <Unknown>Happiness</Unknown>
<Person><Unknown>Hurricane</Unknown> Sandy</Person> relief show. <Unknown>Join</Unknown> us @hotelcafe  rockdrive  friends  help  hurricanesandy
<Unknown>STILL</Unknown> <Unknown>GOING</Unknown> <Unknown>Awake</Unknown> for 32 hours. <Unknown>Partyaaye</Unknown> hardy. I even slept on the floor no shame.  blackfriday  pearls  shopping  nomess  iwassnoringtoo  ohwell  hollahz  pagnit
 <Person>OBAMA</Person>  <Unknown>LMFAO</Unknown>  Winning  <Unknown>Thug</Unknown>
<Unknown>SternShowComiX</Unknown> <Person>Howard AGT Round</Person> 2 @<Unknown>MFBrooklyn</Unknown>  <Unknown>HOWARDSTERN</Unknown>  <Unknown>STERNSHOWCOMIX</Unknown> @zenabuddysgirl @southernjew 
<Unknown>Relationship</Unknown> gt <Unknown>Religion</Unknown>. Good morning 
 <Unknown>AFetusIsAHuman</Unknown>  antiabortion  allWomen  <Unknown>Abolionist</Unknown>  abortion  <Unknown>AbolishHumanAbortion</Unknown>  babies  <Unknown>ChildrenAreABlessing</Unknown>  <Unknown>EndAbortion</Unknown>  <Unknown>Fetus</Unknown>  <Unknown>Love</Unknown>  <Unknown>Miracles</Unknown>  <Unknown>ProLife</Unknown>  <Unknown>StopAbortion</Unknown>  <Unknown>SpeakLife</Unknown>  <Unknown>SaveOurBabies</Unknown>  <Unknown>NationalRightToLife</Unknown>  40dasporlavida  latinobaby  latinababy  40daysforlifeLR  40daysforlife  Prayer  <Unknown>BlackGenocide</Unknown>  blackbaby  whitebabies  <Unknown>BlackWomen</Unknown>  whiteWomen  <Unknown>LatinaWomen</Unknown>  <Unknown>ArkansasRightToLife</Unknown>
Me and @pitbull performing 11 59 in <Location>Montreal</Location>.  globalwarming
 blackfriday  occupy  ola  tents
  34 <Unknown>Da</Unknown> Accessories That Come In L.I.F.E  34  <Unknown>Religion</Unknown>  <Unknown>MercedesVision</Unknown>  <Unknown>Fendi</Unknown>  <Unknown>LVblanket</Unknown>  <Unknown>SF</Unknown>49ers  <Unknown>HallOfFame</Unknown>  S550  <Unknown>Blessed</Unknown>
<Unknown>HAHAHAH</Unknown>  <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> @ caitmurphy @<Unknown>ElenaGornall</Unknown>1 @<Unknown>EmilyStuart</Unknown> X
<Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> in <Unknown>Shibuya</Unknown>  <Location>japan</Location>  hiv  aids  shibuya  instadaily  instapic
Go  <Organization>Argos</Organization> <Unknown>Go</Unknown> workin  39 the social media beat for <Unknown>Grey</Unknown> <Unknown>Cup</Unknown> 2012
She had me at 16 got kick out and beat still didnt get and abortion and still standing strong  tamore  1mother
I shop at the thrift store.. I need these 50 off deals to apply to my bills..  blackfriday
Last night  babyshower  cousin  auntie  lovethem  party  newyork  stophashtagging
 newyork  brooklinbridge  nightime
My girl before her amazing <Person>AGT</Person> performance 
 win  championsleague  zenit
 <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown> The Last One. 
 <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> Less stress. Less pain. Less problems. More <Unknown>Happiness</Unknown>. More <Unknown>Laugh</Unknown>.
Good as you  gay  gayboy  gayboys  gayguys  gaylove  gayrights  gaymarriage  love  lgbt  kissgay  boyloveboy  freedom  freelove
Remember <Person>Harry</Person>  39 s christmas twitcam in 2010
<Unknown>Movember</Unknown> <Unknown>Mustache</Unknown>  november  movember  mustache  men  cancer  donations
<Unknown>Ep</Unknown> 25  lacartafaiR le mini video d  39 un remix avec <Person>Jay</Person> Z pour <Person>Obama</Person> History version 2012 dispo sur http bit.ly <Unknown>TXhiXH</Unknown> ...  ler1er
A scene from <Location>Tahrir Square</Location> on November 27th photographed by <Unknown>TIME</Unknown>  39 s <Person>Bobby Ghosh</Person>. @ghoshworld 
Now this is what pizza should look like  pizza  food  foodporn  goodness  vodka  grandma  angelinas  newyorkpizza
 truth  interesting  abortion  gays  <Location>america</Location>
<Location>Liverpool</Location> players helping <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>Aids</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown>
<Unknown>Download</Unknown> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Person>Movie</Person> <Unknown>Online</Unknown> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> movie download <Unknown>Actors</Unknown> <Unknown>Download</Unknown> here http movynswe.info 1 movie <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Unknown>Review</Unknown> by <Person>Michael Jacobson</Person>. <Location>BARNES</Location> amp amp <Person>NOBLE Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> by <Person>Walt</Person>. <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Person>DVD Movie</Person> <Location>Central SCHOOLHOUSE</Location> <Location>ROCK</Location> <Unknown>ELECTION</Unknown> <Unknown>COLLECTION</Unknown>. <Organization>Amazon.com</Organization> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Unknown>Classroom</Unknown>. Buy <Unknown>Download</Unknown> or <Unknown>Rent</Unknown> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> The <Unknown>Election</Unknown>. Considering the age and modest origins . <Unknown>Aspect</Unknown> <Unknown>Ratio</Unknown> 1.33 1 <Unknown>Description</Unknown>. <Unknown>Rent</Unknown> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> The <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> P amp amp S <Person>DVD</Person> and over 100 000 other movies at <Organization>Blockbuster</Organization>. <Unknown>Video</Unknown>. Get ready to cast a vote for <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> . . <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> The <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> P amp amp S <Person>DVD Rental</Person> <Unknown>Rent</Unknown>. So we wont tell anyone if some of the parents sit down with. Among them are  039 I  039 m Just A <Person>Bill</Person>. <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Person>Movie</Person> Mom <Unknown>Beliefnet</Unknown>.com Even grown ups are having a tough time staying on top of this years historic <Unknown>Presidential</Unknown> election. Fourteen irresistible class songs like I  039 m Just a <Person>Bill</Person> The <Unknown>Preamble</Unknown> and I  039 m <Unknown>Gonna</Unknown> <Location>Send</Location> Your. <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> Now On <Person>DVD Walt Disney</Person>. <Unknown>Video</Unknown> amp amp <Unknown>Audio</Unknown> These cartoons are. and classic songs that celebrate everything that makes our country great in <Person>SCHOOLHOUSE</Person> <Location>ROCK</Location> THE <Unknown>ELECTION</Unknown> <Unknown>COLLECTION</Unknown> <Organization>Amazon.com</Organization> <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Person>Jack Sheldon</Person>. <Person>Schoolhouse</Person> <Location>Rock</Location> The <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Collection</Unknown> <Person>Walt Disney</Person> Studios <Unknown>Home</Unknown> <Unknown>Entertainment</Unknown> <Unknown>Unrated</Unknown> September 23 2008 List <Unknown>Price</Unknown> 
 galatasaray  championsleague
The <Unknown>DIVA</Unknown> @dayofthediva on a poster for a gig at <Organization>Eagle Manchester</Organization> for <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown>. @katherineellis1
Every  <Person>BlackFriday</Person> shopping spree should include a stop here @1<Unknown>DWorldMerch</Unknown>  onedirection
@lukebullock With <Person>OBama</Person>
Really bitch? Daisy is the sleep police and owner of the jerk store.
<Unknown>AHH</Unknown> the winter mornings lt 3  <Unknown>Decemberwish</Unknown> @soppphhhh  39 its so fucking cold  39 
Never too late lmao  <Person>Obama</Person>  <Unknown>KevinHa</Unknown>  <Unknown>RP</Unknown>
My <Unknown>Cyber</Unknown> Monday purchase My blue <Organization>Police Box</Organization> leggings....well as I like to say <Unknown>Tardis</Unknown> leggings Thank you @blackmilkclothing for this awesomeness 
@vaneycj y aids
And <Person>Obama</Person> said 
The key to rocking it this early in the morning is staying up all night @todayshow  yolo  globalwarming
<Unknown>Alinin</Unknown> telefonundan  galatasaray  championsleague  cimbom  cimbombom  ultraaslan  instagram
<Unknown>Horse</Unknown> shoes on my ass true religion jeans  true
 bird  seaguls  malibu in  november  globalwarming
Quite a few cameras here for the announcement on ocean acidification.  WA  <Location>Seattle</Location>  tvnews  globalwarming  photographers
Of course @allietotheb wears band aids made of silver...  radness
I shit you not...most great brains in human history have been skeptical about religion amp <Unknown>God</Unknown>
 nofilter  <Unknown>Browns</Unknown>  <Organization>NFL  Cleveland</Organization>  <Unknown>GoBrowns</Unknown>
 <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Birthday</Unknown> To Me  <Unknown>TqALLAH</Unknown>  <Unknown>LoveISLAM</Unknown>  <Unknown>LoveUallLillahiTaala</Unknown>
 <Person>Obama</Person> approves  <Unknown>WhoDat</Unknown> <Unknown>Love</Unknown>
<Unknown>Happening</Unknown> now Come on down <Unknown>Dank</Unknown> and the <Unknown>Funksticks</Unknown> are on stage  <Person>sandy</Person>  benefit
Election night
<Unknown>Mohamed</Unknown> <Unknown>Mahmoud</Unknown> 2012  protest  police  riot  revolution  tahrir  clashes  <Location>cairo</Location>  <Location>egypt</Location>  egyptian  me  usefsalah  ua07  march  acab  anarchy  youth  photography  photographer  photooftheday  picoftheday  instagram  instacanvas  teargas  graffiti  strong  soldiers  filmmaker  cinema  followme  chants
Best uniform in the <Organization>NFL</Organization>.
        <Location>bahrain</Location>
<Unknown>NOM</Unknown> DE LA <Unknown>MARQUE</Unknown> religion <Unknown>TAILLE</Unknown> 36 38 P.A 280 P.V 150 <Unknown>ADRESSE</Unknown> <Unknown>EMAIL</Unknown> coralie.debeque@gmail.com
My grandma is the sweetest lady I know. She is currently battling cancer and has her final tests this week to see if there are any last possibilities to help her Say a prayer for her today please 
For those people who have said I disrespect religion amp religious people shhh I do 
<Unknown>Bush</Unknown> was far more denigrated than <Person>Obama</Person>  <Person>JEZEBEL</Person>  tcot  sgp  teaparty
Trying to explain theater techniques but lacking proper visual aids? Check out <Unknown>Chekov</Unknown>  39 s Guns.
Love this city.  newyork
<Location>Cotton</Location> <Person>Candy</Person> in <Location>Cairo</Location> <Unknown>LOL</Unknown>
<Person>RIP Young</Person> Prince you will be missed young homie He died of cat cancer.  <Unknown>CureFIP</Unknown>
 <Organization>Philippine Crame Church</Organization> police 
Let  39 s conquer cancer event w  alexthao  terryhe amp  shimmycocopuffsss
Seen this on twitter what in the dilly dally shilly shally do chix be thinking after they get an abortion ?
<Person>Pandora</Person> is sucking up to me with its advertising since I boycotted them during election season with their <Person>Obama</Person> nonsense.
4 <Unknown>BUNDLE</Unknown> <Unknown>DEAL</Unknown>  lavishemporium  boutique  blackfriday  blackfridaysale  blackfriday2012  thanksgiving  thanksgivingsale  cybermonday  armcandy  accessories  brazilianhair  curlyhair  handbags  idohair  isellhair  indianhair  jewelry  kinkyhair  laceclosures  malaysianhair  order  peruvianhair  quality  sale  shoes  straighthair  virginhair  virginextensions  wavyhair
 <Unknown>Dogs</Unknown>  <Unknown>Cute</Unknown>  <Unknown>MobCam</Unknown>  <Unknown>InstaDogs</Unknown>  <Unknown>InstaAnimals</Unknown>  <Person>Adorable  Pets</Person>  <Unknown>FoundAndLost</Unknown>
<Unknown>Post</Unknown> election rice @suculentBCN
 newyork  m amp m  39 s
There it is  backyard  bar  parkslope  <Location>brooklyn</Location>  newyork  brunch  egg  yolk  yum  food  foodporn
<Unknown>Finna</Unknown> go to <Unknown>Raising</Unknown> <Unknown>Canes</Unknown> <Unknown>Im</Unknown> starving Created with the <Unknown>Free</Unknown> @<Unknown>Versagram</Unknown> <Unknown>App</Unknown>  vbf1  blackfriday  shopping  leftovers  text  versagram  versalove
Work flowww  bakers  blackfriday   death
Why couldn  039 t this movie be my birthday gift? reproachful look @<Unknown>RealHughJackman</Unknown>  decemberwish
In <Location>Japan</Location> watching the election? Should be able to remote vote <Person>Gotta</Person> be an app for that lol
 fuckoff  <Person>Zimmerman</Person> you  deserve  life. amp that  photo of  you  only being  released  now ?  so  staged  lame  killer  poor  trayvon
<Unknown>Pra</Unknown> alguem que agt conhece ou nem?????? @ligatti 
 <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown>
One erection gay  gayboy  gayboys  gayguys  gaymarriage  gayrights  freedom  freelove  street  lgbt  love  onedirection  harrystyles  luoisthomilison
<Organization>Teenage Cancer Trust</Organization> 2nd year with @professorgreen
<Organization>Subway</Organization> stories vol.1 @zlbg @frsharabianluv  subway  nyc  newyork
<Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Dvdrip</Unknown> <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> movie download <Unknown>Actors</Unknown> <Person>Eihi</Person> <Unknown>Shiina</Unknown> <Unknown>Cay</Unknown> <Person>Izumi Mame</Person> <Unknown>Yamada</Unknown> <Unknown>Yukihide</Unknown> <Person>Benny Ikuko Sawada</Person> <Unknown>Itsuji</Unknown> <Unknown>Itao</Unknown> <Unknown>Akane</Unknown> <Unknown>Akanezawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Ayano</Unknown> <Unknown>Yamamoto</Unknown> <Unknown>Jiji</Unknown> <Person>B Tsugumi</Person> <Unknown>Nagasawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Download</Unknown> here http molsdvcery.info 1 movie <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Bloody</Unknown> good <Organization>New York Post</Organization> <Unknown>Strap</Unknown> yourselves in boys and girls because things are about to get very very bloody and very very strange. April 26 2008. <Unknown>Actors</Unknown> <Person>Eihi</Person> <Unknown>Shiina</Unknown> <Unknown>Ruka</Unknown> <Unknown>Itsuji</Unknown> <Unknown>Itao</Unknown> <Unknown>Keyman</Unknown> <Unknown>Yukihide</Unknown> <Person>Benny Tokyo</Person> <Organization>Police</Organization> Chief <Unknown>Jiji</Unknown> <Person>B Barabara</Person> <Unknown>Man</Unknown> <Person>Ikuko Sawada</Person> <Unknown>Bar</Unknown>. Amid a campaign to privatise the police force the city is struck by a. <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Wikipedia</Unknown> the free encyclopedia <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Tky</Unknown> <Unknown>Zankoku</Unknown> <Unknown>Keisatsu</Unknown> ? is a 2008 Japanese American gore film co written edited and directed by <Unknown>Yoshihiro</Unknown> <Unknown>Nishimura</Unknown> and. <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> 2008 <Unknown>IMDb</Unknown> Director <Unknown>Yoshihiro</Unknown> <Unknown>Nishimura</Unknown>. Coming from the people that brought us The <Unknown>Machine</Unknown> <Unknown>Girl</Unknown> it is no surprise that <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> has the cult following that it does.. <Unknown>Tky</Unknown> <Unknown>Zankoku</Unknown> <Unknown>Keisatsu</Unknown> <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Person>Movie</Person> <Unknown>Reviews</Unknown>. <Unknown>Twitch</Unknown> Best <Unknown>Asian</Unknown> <Unknown>Film</Unknown>. <Unknown>Tky</Unknown> <Unknown>Zankoku</Unknown> <Unknown>Keisatsu</Unknown> <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Rotten</Unknown> <Unknown>Tomatoes</Unknown> <Unknown>Review</Unknown> A mad scientist known as <Unknown>Key</Unknown> <Unknown>Man</Unknown> has created a rampaging virus that mutates unsuspecting humans into nightmarish abominations of nature and in order... <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Organization>Netflix Tokyo</Organization> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> When crazed scientist <Unknown>Key</Unknown> <Unknown>Man</Unknown> develops a virus that causes humans to mutate samurai sword wielding cop <Unknown>Ruka</Unknown> is called in to annihilate the. <Organization>Amazon.com Tokyo</Organization> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Blu</Unknown> <Person>ray Eihi</Person> <Unknown>Shiina</Unknown> <Unknown>Yoshihiro</Unknown>. But... That  039 s one word to say after this master  039 s class in splatter fest ends. <Location>Tokyo</Location> <Unknown>Gore</Unknown> <Organization>Police</Organization> <Unknown>Reviews</Unknown> amp amp Ratings <Unknown>IMDb</Unknown> <Unknown>Review</Unknown> the title says it all and it lives up to its title Wow
S pra quem pode... @<Unknown>WesleySafadao</Unknown> amp @<Unknown>GarotaSafada</Unknown>  app  android
<Unknown>Raised</Unknown> 150 for prostate cancer and got a ton of tabs for <Person>Ronald McDonald</Person> 
@kylegibbons @jelluhfish aids. X
Thank you to all the fans for their donations at yesterday  39 s food drive to benefit those affected by  <Unknown>HurricaneSandy</Unknown>  <Unknown>UConnCountry</Unknown>  <Unknown>BleedBlue</Unknown>
<Unknown>Lsb</Unknown> love  lsb  girllovegirl  gay  gayboy  gayguys  gaylove  gayrights  gaymarriage  freedom  freelove  love  lgbt
Call airpopolice ..
@movember <Unknown>Day</Unknown> 16  movember  cancer sucks
Best election day look my great aunt <Unknown>Doad</Unknown> soon to be 100 voted <Person>Obama</Person> in her blue parka
 <Unknown>Mexes</Unknown>  <Unknown>Chilena</Unknown>  <Unknown>Francia</Unknown>  <Unknown>Italia</Unknown>  <Location>Venezuela</Location>  <Person>UCL  ChampionsLeague</Person>  <Unknown>Calcio</Unknown>  <Unknown>Futbol</Unknown>  <Unknown>ACMilan</Unknown>  <Unknown>Golazo</Unknown>  <Unknown>Gol</Unknown>  <Unknown>ForzaMilan</Unknown>  <Unknown>Rossonero</Unknown>
Love is my religion.
<Unknown>Hunting</Unknown> <Unknown>Trophy</Unknown> quot just kept <Unknown>SWELLING</Unknown> poor varMITT @exposeLiberal @co2hog  P2  tcot  teaparty  gop  <Unknown>DEMS</Unknown>  <Unknown>LIBERAL</Unknown>
 memoriesIwontforget
Raising money for <Organization>Teenage Cancer Trust</Organization>
<Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> square <Unknown>AGAIN</Unknown>  <Location>egypt</Location>  tahrir  <Location>cairo</Location>  revolution  ihatemuslimbrotherhood  freedom  freeegypt  instagram  instalife
Amen To That @spawnio20  <Location>City</Location>  <Person>CL  ChampionsLeague</Person>
<Unknown>Equality</Unknown> breakfast  gay  gayboy  gayboys  gayguys  gaylove  gayrights  gaymarriage  kissgay  freelove  freedom  lgbt
<Unknown>Cheeee</Unknown> ... oh hey there  39 s <Person>Micky</Person> mouse <Person>P  NewYork</Person>  newyorkcity  <Person>NYC  TimeSquare</Person>  selfie  city  <Person>micky</Person>  mickymouse
Good bonding weekend with daddy  <Person>BlackFriday</Person>  shopping  golf
 kaka  thebest  bernabeu  championsleague  realmadrid
pantallazo a la trasmisin en directo desde la plaza  <Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> en el <Location>Cairo</Location>  egipto http reuters.livestation.com demo
This Actually Made My <Unknown>Hea</Unknown> <Unknown>Smile</Unknown>... @kinggoldchains @tyga @kingcairo  <Unknown>SoSweet</Unknown>  <Unknown>Tyga</Unknown>  <Location>Cairo</Location>  King  Studio  <Unknown>Family</Unknown>  <Unknown>Love</Unknown>  <Unknown>Baby</Unknown>  <Unknown>LastKings</Unknown>  <Unknown>Kingin</Unknown>  <Unknown>HardWork</Unknown>  <Unknown>Small</Unknown>  <Unknown>Happy</Unknown>
Next year breast cancer helmets ewwww
Ok so the  <Unknown>Barberton</Unknown>  police pulled this old lady over in the parking lot of  <Unknown>KMa</Unknown>. Then a police  <Unknown>SUV</Unknown> amp another crusier comes amp blocks her in like she has  drugs or  guns Then they ler her go without a  ticket.  taxdollarsatwork
 taken by me <Unknown>Global</Unknown> warming at it  39 s finest. <Location>Baltimore</Location>  <Unknown>GlobalWarming</Unknown>
<Person>LLS Call</Person> me <Person>Sandy</Person> <Unknown>Little</Unknown> <Unknown>Cheeks</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Sign</Unknown> outside of the  abortion clinic today  oxymoronic
Ghost corner. <Location>Cairo</Location> <Location>Illinois</Location>.
<Unknown>Repost</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Election</Unknown> <Unknown>Day</Unknown> <Unknown>VOTE</Unknown>
I can watch this paover and over again  <Unknown>CountryStrong</Unknown>  Travis  cutie  cancer  favorite
I might just fall asleep waiting for this game lol  nfl  nyg  gmen  football  sunday  funday
 cristians  muslims  religion  church  mosk  extremist  terrorist  911  wtc  binladen  osama  osamabinladen  alqaeda  alqaida  <Person>al</Person> kaida  mudjahedin  taliban  revolution  ignorence  nonesense
<Unknown>Red</Unknown> <Unknown>White</Unknown> and <Unknown>Blue</Unknown> Christmas Tree in honor of the re election of President <Person>Barack Obama</Person>.
@bigtiggershow <Unknown>Hey</Unknown> Big <Unknown>Bro</Unknown> Please DM <Unknown>Ur</Unknown> <Unknown>Gmail</Unknown> So I Can <Location>Send</Location> <Person>U My</Person> <Organization>New</Organization> <Person>HIV</Person> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Awareness</Unknown> <Unknown>Record</Unknown> I Need An <Unknown>Interview</Unknown>
I  39 d love another little adventure  <Location>Rome</Location>  <Person>Newyork</Person>
 <Unknown>Talvez</Unknown> nao seje <Person>nessa</Person> <Person>vida</Person> ainda mas vc ainda vai ser a minha <Person>vida</Person> entao agt vai fugir pro mar e eu vou pedir pra namorar vc vai me dizer que vai pensar e no fim vai deixar 8 
Please get better my big man cuddle up with me I love you <Person>Henry</Person> hate cancer 
 <Organization>New</Organization>  <Person>Zimmerman</Person> <Unknown>Dj</Unknown> <Unknown>Clue</Unknown> voice ... they say this what the lil homie  <Unknown>Trayvon</Unknown> did b4 he got clipped <Unknown>BUT</Unknown> that still dont change the fact this clown chased <Unknown>Trayvon</Unknown> down w the toast when cops on the phone told him <Unknown>STOP</Unknown> so ... <Unknown>GUILTY</Unknown> 
We can all test the claims of  religion don  039 t let them get away with telling you <Person>tales</Person>. atheism
 <Unknown>Hryda</Unknown>  onmyPboishit  thuglifer  <Person>Blackfriday</Person>  imblackeveryday  blacksheep  backonmyfeet  stillupstillaintwent2sleep  <Unknown>Jumma</Unknown>  prayerday  <Person>Rip</Person>  V12<Unknown>BmR</Unknown>
Finally My Pro Same Sex <Unknown>Marriage</Unknown> <Unknown>Shiis</Unknown> Here <Unknown>FCKH</Unknown>8.<Unknown>COM</Unknown>  gaymarriage  equality  fckh8  gay  lesbian  <Unknown>LGBT</Unknown> I don  39 t love because of what you are it  39 s because of who you are.
I have the best grandmother ever Thanks <Person>Bibi  BlackFriday</Person>  <Unknown>Love</Unknown>  Amazing
Dixie gurdwara in my textbook world religion class  uoft
Party hard f ck the police  party
 tbt Halloween  weathermen  hurricaneSandy
<Unknown>NAO</Unknown> <Unknown>MOLE</Unknown> <Unknown>NAO</Unknown> <Unknown>DIRETORIA</Unknown> E O <Unknown>CANCER</Unknown> <Unknown>DO</Unknown> <Unknown>VERDAO</Unknown> 
Put your hands up in the air. Put your hands up In the air  budha  religion  incense  techno  song  memories
The best night ever D
 <Unknown>DecemberWish</Unknown> Less stress. Less pain. Less problems. Less tears. More happiness. More laugh. More love... 
<Person>GEORGE ZIMMERMAN</Person> <Unknown>REALLY</Unknown>? ? I <Unknown>HOPE</Unknown> <Unknown>THEY</Unknown> <Unknown>LOCK</Unknown> U UP FOR <Unknown>LIFE</Unknown>  <Unknown>JUSTICE</Unknown>
my little man rocking <Unknown>Burberry</Unknown> <Unknown>True</Unknown> <Unknown>Religion</Unknown> and Olympics. sho cute.
Spending  34 <Unknown>QT</Unknown>  34 with the <Unknown>Boo</Unknown> watching some football  nfl  cfl  football  qualitytime  putaringonit 
An <Person>African</Person> <Unknown>Election</Unknown>
 architecture  postsandy  hurricanesandy  nj
@<Unknown>PhonseeMac</Unknown>  <Unknown>HeyBoo</Unknown> quot @ <Unknown>YouLoveShauna</Unknown> I need a cancer bf. We  039 d be perfect for each other. quot 
@justinbieber and I just casually chillen with <Person>Obama</Person>.
 <Unknown>Decemberwish</Unknown>  december  ig  igers  igdaily  photodaily  mymonth  hashtags  nofilter  tweegram  instagood  instagram  instamood  instalikes  instaphoto  instafamous  instafollow  followforfollow  likesforlikes  f4f  l4l  10likes  smile  happy
I heard there  39 s a gas problem in <Person>NYC</Person>.  <Person>sandy</Person>  ny  nyc
And these bitches be lettin em..  repost @<Person>dat</Person> nigga mase  <Unknown>Magic</Unknown>  <Person>Johnson  HIV  Aids</Person>  <Unknown>OhBabyiLikeItRaw</Unknown>
<Unknown>Hahahaha</Unknown> good joke  fantasy  abortion  flop  nfl  fantasyfootball
Deliveries to make <Unknown>Snacks</Unknown> to eat  pinkelly  oreos  hurricanesandy
<Unknown>Ur</Unknown>  <Unknown>Funny</Unknown>  <Person>Football</Person>  <Unknown>CyberGift</Unknown>  Troops  <Person>ISS  Seahawks</Person> myCancer <Unknown>Journey</Unknown> http kingkaps7.mysite.com journal 817347 
 tree  snow  ig  igers  instagram  fallentree  hurricanesandy  <Person>sandy</Person>  winter  autumn  seasons  jj  photooftheday  likeforlike  picoftheday  leaves  cold
9 months later. One <Unknown>Election</Unknown> later. Have you forgotten? I haven  39 t...  <Unknown>TrayvonMartin</Unknown>
farafesh
For the collection  hellokitty  newyork  shotglass
Bad religion
It  39 s  <Unknown>FashionablyDelicious</Unknown>  oakville  cancer  fundraiser
My  <Person>BlackFriday</Person>  purchases made at 2am at the mall...  lol @sephora @freshfounder @lushvalleyfair @julepmaven
<Person>Obama</Person>  <Unknown>Aughhhhh</Unknown> @<Unknown>Kingcairo</Unknown>
I look up  39 One Direction  39 on playlist.com and I see this. <Unknown>Congrats</Unknown> One Direction you  39 re so hot that you have diagnosed us <Unknown>Directioners</Unknown> with <Unknown>Ovarian</Unknown> <Unknown>Cancer</Unknown>.
<Unknown>Rocking</Unknown> my 99 problems but mitt ain  39 t 1 tee  <Person>Obama</Person>
 lt 3 <Location>PARIS</Location> <Person><Unknown>SAINT</Unknown> GERMAIN</Person> lt 3  <Unknown>PSG</Unknown>  <Unknown>PSGPORTO</Unknown>  C1  <Person>Championsleague</Person>  <Unknown>Win</Unknown>  <Location>Paris</Location>
They caught us discussing our election predictions. <Unknown>LOL</Unknown>
<Organization>AIDS Project Los Angeles</Organization> <Unknown>World</Unknown> <Organization>AIDS</Organization> <Unknown>Day</Unknown>  <Unknown>FoodDrive</Unknown> is this Sat. 12 1 from 10 4pm More <Unknown>Info</Unknown> apla.org fooddrive 
 breast  cancer  awareness  soccer  game  vsyulee  november27th  bethere  shootout  prizes  530  720  wearpink
 <Unknown>Tahrir</Unknown> square  Today  27November2012  protest  revolution  <Location>Tahrir  Square</Location>  <Location>Cairo</Location>  <Location>Egypt</Location>  tahrirsquare  brutal  police  force  teargas  gas
<Unknown>MESSAGE</Unknown> TO THE <Unknown>PRESIDENT</Unknown> <Unknown>AT</Unknown> <Unknown>STARBUCKS</Unknown>
<Unknown>Por</Unknown> los nios <Person>con</Person> cancer @karemcitac @pabloacap
<Unknown>Ladies</Unknown> and gentlemen your First Lady.  firstlady  obama  michelleobama  merica  <Location>usa</Location>
This how you know this girl was never pregnant OR have an abortion. No one describes an abortion as  34 decent  34 . Not to mention you scheduled the  34 abortion  34 mon had the consultation tues and the procedure wed? Where dey do that at?  <Unknown>GTFOH</Unknown>  <Unknown>TheThirst</Unknown>
The day I realized I was growing up  <Unknown>MemoriesIWontForget</Unknown>  <Unknown>Graduation</Unknown>2011 @unibocconi
This is what he said he wanted to  read tonight.  <Unknown>AudacityOfHope</Unknown>  <Person>Obama</Person>  <Unknown>BarackObama</Unknown>  <Unknown>ProudDad</Unknown>
 decemberwish meet this <Unknown>Oppa</Unknown> 
<Unknown>Souls</Unknown> up spirit is back back to the good old days  tahrir  <Location>egypt</Location>  <Location>cairo</Location>  travel
I  039 ve become lost in an anti <Person>Obama</Person> <Unknown>FB</Unknown> page that one of my cousins quot liked quot . I love that this guy  039 s name is <Person>Joe Dirt</Person>. 
<Unknown>Rap</Unknown> And <Unknown>Religion</Unknown> book release party @ The Diplomat
I hereby declare that I will not revenge antagonise football fans
<Organization>Flag Football Skills Clinic</Organization> 
@<Unknown>GoT</Unknown> Cast <Unknown>GoT</Unknown> Cast at the <Unknown>Game</Unknown> of <Unknown>Thrones</Unknown> <Unknown>Premiere</Unknown> at <Unknown>SF</Unknown>. http t.co <Unknown>BM</Unknown>0<Unknown>Jh</Unknown>4<Unknown>QYkU</Unknown>
@telltalegames holy smokes telltale. <Unknown>Game</Unknown> of thrones just keeps getting better and better. <Unknown>Amaaaazing</Unknown> job 
@<Unknown>SarahSarah</Unknown>256 @<Unknown>WinceyWillis</Unknown>1 <Location>India</Location> has a high percentage of mega millionaires an we still provide aid Give it to all the animals I vote
@dallxscxm @<Unknown>YourBoyMyles</Unknown> its where all the animals are 
@<Unknown>InnovativeHindu</Unknown> @ndtv @<Unknown>Headlinestoday</Unknown> <Unknown>Muslim</Unknown> <Unknown>Org</Unknown> <Unknown>PFI</Unknown> has attacked n vandalised the <Unknown>Hindu</Unknown> <Location>Temple</Location> in <Location>Calicut</Location> <Unknown>Kozhikode</Unknown> on Sunday http 
Football Season Coming Up Soon 
@<Unknown>RyanBrownWJOX</Unknown> @<Unknown>JayHopeIsHere</Unknown> @<Person>Joey</Person>35209 You dont think the <Unknown>UABOT</Unknown> has kept <Unknown>UAB</Unknown> s football program down? Come on man.
@<Unknown>JeffSolochek</Unknown> <Location>Florida</Location> superintendents school board members raise more  testing concerns recommendations @<Unknown>ErikaDonalds</Unknown>  edFL http t.
@<Unknown>SteveStfler</Unknown> <Unknown>BRUH</Unknown> THE EDUCATION <Unknown>SYSTEM</Unknown> <Unknown>FAILING</Unknown> http t.co <Unknown>SkMUpn</Unknown>61jb
@<Unknown>SDLPlive</Unknown> .@gerardmcd93 <Organization>SDLP</Organization> have taken action on poverty by introducing the living wage in <Location>belfast</Location> and mid <Unknown>Ulster</Unknown> council. @<Unknown>Mencap</Unknown> <Unknown>NI</Unknown> 
@<Unknown>AnishNation</Unknown> <Unknown>Job</Unknown> opportunity Education <Unknown>Development</Unknown> <Unknown>Officer</Unknown> <Unknown>Nipissing</Unknown> <Unknown>Campus</Unknown> http t.co bINn0ubQdi via @sharethis
<Person>Robby Ratan</Person> is here talking about  avatars in  education. @<Unknown>MSUComArtSci</Unknown>  <Unknown>MSU</Unknown> <Unknown>ITL</Unknown> http t.co tvcFNplp1I
<Person>Will</Person> the @<Unknown>NYSenate</Unknown> stand w 63 of <Organization>New</Organization> Yorkers who oppose @<Unknown>NYGovCuomo</Unknown> s education agenda? Contact your legislator now http t.co 7<Unknown>RqvlR</Unknown>0eq7
http t.co <Unknown>RTeNnDFVuu</Unknown>  <Unknown>Sale</Unknown>  <Person>Allen Edmonds</Person> <Unknown>GRIDIRON</Unknown> <Unknown>Oxfords</Unknown> 7.5 <Person>D Brown Football</Person> <Location>Grain</Location> <Unknown>Leather</Unknown> 241 
@<Unknown>StPetePD</Unknown> arrest 2 for  animalcruelty when more than 40 animals found uncared for. http t.co u0<Unknown>IoMyKr</Unknown>61 http t.co bvDrIvp1<Unknown>Rp</Unknown>
Here is an updated version of <Unknown>Game</Unknown> of <Unknown>Thrones</Unknown> <Unknown>Bingo</Unknown> on sale for 1.99 https t.co <Unknown>SteyDsxjem</Unknown> @<Unknown>GameOfThrones</Unknown> @<Unknown>GRRMspeaking</Unknown>
25 Then And Now <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> Of <Unknown>Bollywood</Unknown> <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> You Will Get Shocked http t.co <Unknown>WwGkNRZsai</Unknown>
@<Unknown>JeanneBartram</Unknown> <Person>Iain Duncan Smith</Person> ignores food bank charity and meets with bankers about poverty instead http t.co g7I4<Unknown>RbatPd</Unknown>
@zepvv I hope he is. I d retire from international football immediately tbh. Sounds like he s got serious potential which won t be helped..
@allthelovelouis what if <Person>harry</Person> goes to <Person>louis</Person> football game and starts cheerleading on the sidelines like he did back in 2012
@90sfootball <Unknown>Retweet</Unknown> if you remember watching <Person>James Richardson</Person> sit outside an Italian cafe reading the papers on <Person>Football</Person> <Unknown>Italia</Unknown> http 
@<Person>angela</Person> std Animals are here with us not for us  <Unknown>ApoyoLeyAnimal</Unknown>087 http t.co U9lzybxi1o
@<Unknown>EssexFBU</Unknown> <Unknown>Brigade</Unknown> reps on  <Unknown>FBU</Unknown> education course @<Unknown>WortleyHall</Unknown> suppo <Unknown>EssexFBU</Unknown> <Unknown>Control</Unknown> staff pledge donations  <Unknown>NotGoingAway</Unknown> http t.
I wanna got to <Unknown>Baylor</Unknown> to play football of <Location>Texas</Location> 
 We <Unknown>Pray</Unknown> for <Unknown>Daily</Unknown> <Unknown>Bread</Unknown> http t.co cS0ovAd4<Unknown>JX</Unknown>  poverty  hunger  <Unknown>WhyWePray</Unknown>
Education costs money. But then so does ignorance.
<Organization>University of Saskatchewan</Organization> students protest rising tuition fees call for free education http t.co <Unknown>VxPbn</Unknown>35nWy
@rightsnet <Person>Iain Duncan Smith</Person> refuses to meet with food bank charity @<Unknown>TrussellTrust</Unknown> http t.co qjVDxOAKaS
<Unknown>ORGY</Unknown> <Unknown>PORGY</Unknown> <Unknown>European</Unknown> <Unknown>Invasion</Unknown> <Person>DNA Reveals</Person> The <Unknown>Origins</Unknown> Of <Unknown>Modern</Unknown> Europeans <Unknown>IFLScience</Unknown> http t.co mmz8<Unknown>VLmbiN</Unknown>
ndtv <Location>Japan</Location> tops in technology transfer pacts <Organization>Reserve Bank of India</Organization> http t.co <Unknown>Jgr</Unknown>8utquw1 http t.co <Unknown>ZbnoUr</Unknown>7oO7 
@<Organization>MindyRosier Read Public Education</Organization> <Unknown>Warriors</Unknown> <Unknown>Unite</Unknown>  <Unknown>AllKidsNeedht</Unknown> @quadgurl @<Unknown>CMZR</Unknown> @<Unknown>RodneyJordan</Unknown>4 @<Unknown>TruthinTeaching</Unknown> @teachin1100 http
@philo quotes The most important paof education is proper training in the nursery. <Person>Plato</Person> http t.co z7M3qBZZId
ndtv  <Unknown>NationalAwards</Unknown> actor <Unknown>Priyanka</Unknown> <Unknown>Chopra</Unknown> hails small town girl <Unknown>Kangana</Unknown> <Unknown>Ranaut</Unknown> http t.co gn33k8teb1 http t.co fYpmyVtzQ2 
Domestic violence stems from a womans financial dependence on a man. Give a woman education shell never depend on a man for livelihood
 <Unknown>Man</Unknown> <Unknown>Ki</Unknown> <Unknown>Baat</Unknown> A talk from the heaby the Prime Minister <Unknown>Narendra</Unknown> <Unknown>Modi</Unknown> on All <Organization>India Radio</Organization> <Unknown>News</Unknown>
@outlawvern One comment so far on my <Unknown>SHE</Unknown> <Person>S GOTTA</Person> <Unknown>HAVE</Unknown> IT review so I m sure today s <Location>HOLLYWOOD</Location> <Unknown>SHUFFLE</Unknown> one will be a smash. http t.co
He s landed in <Location>Hollywood</Location> Look for @dneedles12 live repofrom LA tonight on @<Unknown>WISN</Unknown>12<Unknown>News</Unknown> at 6 as the  <Unknown>Badgers</Unknown> prepare for the  <Unknown>Sweet</Unknown>16
@<Unknown>Okies</Unknown>4<Person>Carrie Carrie Underwood</Person> I <Unknown>Told</Unknown> You So <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Bowl</Unknown> <Unknown>Surprise</Unknown> <Unknown>Guest</Unknown> <Person>Mr. Randy Travis</Person> <Person>WOW Amazing</Person> https t.co a2c7Z
@<Unknown>NBCLA</Unknown> WATCH  <Unknown>WillFerrell</Unknown> receives <Location>Hollywood</Location> Walk of <Unknown>Fame</Unknown> star celebrates with family. http t.co xBqXi5xSWM http t.co 3zEbbW7X7P
@<Unknown>RevRichardColes</Unknown> I could watch <Person>Paul Hollywood</Person> make mille feuilles all day long. But I am no more likely to make it myself than refine m
 <Organization>Hollywood  Star Interview Magazine</Organization> January 1995 <Person>Julia Roberts</Person> <Person>Tim Robbins</Person> <Person>Laurence Fishburne</Person> http t.co <Unknown>XaXZK</Unknown>2<Unknown>IFRq</Unknown>  <Unknown>BestSeller</Unknown>  <Organization>eBay</Organization>
I m now an A List celebrity in <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location>. You can be famous too by playing on iPhone http t.co sb0xCw01Q0
@<Unknown>BrooksBeau</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> smells like weed
<Person>Mr. Hollywood</Person> s next Mega <Unknown>Deal</Unknown> is this Thursday <Location>March</Location> 26 <Unknown>Join</Unknown> the event for important reminders on this gluten... http t.co uEUA19<Unknown>IWUr</Unknown>
@<Unknown>JBCrewdotcom</Unknown> <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> of <Person>Justin Bieber</Person> leaving 1<Unknown>Oak</Unknown> in <Location>West Hollywood</Location> CA. March 21 http t.co u32s15qSLr
@dollllllfaceee Yes I still play <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location>.
@<Unknown>TheAegiMaster</Unknown> Been to <Unknown>Harlem</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Person>Jackson Mississippi</Person> 
 <Unknown>Singer</Unknown>  <Unknown>Actress</Unknown> <Unknown>Breakout</Unknown> by  <Unknown>MileyCyrus</Unknown>  <Person>CD Jul</Person> 2008 <Location>Hollywood</Location> 0.55 0 Bids End Date http t.co hkyq83sYrs  <Unknown>Deals</Unknown>  <Unknown>Bargains</Unknown>
@Lady9<Unknown>NewOrleans</Unknown> It s not a new thing though. <Location>Hollywood</Location> has long had a history of emasculating black men by having them play womanly roles
@<Unknown>Iam</Unknown>1izzo Big S O 2 @<Unknown>LeoDiCaprio</Unknown> for getting the young R B celebrities ready for  <Location>Hollywood</Location>  <Unknown>YoungHollywood</Unknown>  <Unknown>NextUp</Unknown>  <Unknown>Movies</Unknown> @etnow  <Unknown>TM</Unknown>
@<Unknown>DuncanWhitehead</Unknown> One of the best  whodunnit  mystery  books of the decade. <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Times</Unknown>  kindleespaol  kindleunlimited  kindle 
 <Person>jesu Young</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> launches celebrity focused content on <Organization>Apple TV Apple TV</Organization> is getting its own celeb... http t.co <Unknown>CUzAu</Unknown>8w5ho  paulz
@Big12<Unknown>SportsESPN</Unknown> He s landed in <Location>Hollywood</Location> Look for @dneedles12 live repofrom LA tonight on @<Unknown>WISN</Unknown>12<Unknown>News</Unknown> at 6 as the  <Unknown>Badgers</Unknown> prepare
 <Person>jesu Young</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location> launches celebrity focused content on <Organization>Apple TV Apple TV</Organization> is getting its own celeb... http t.co 8pgmwwgOkl  paulz
@<Unknown>JOPDreke</Unknown> We ve <Unknown>Exposed</Unknown> The Secret Behind <Person>Liam Many</Person> <Unknown>Other</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Celebs</Unknown> <Unknown>Explosive</Unknown> <Unknown>Muscle</Unknown> Gains http t.co <Unknown>XhzqBo</Unknown>0j9h http t.co
http t.co hf8h7<Unknown>IuGc</Unknown>6 <Location>HOLLYWOOD</Location> <Unknown>COLLAGE</Unknown> <Unknown>POSTER</Unknown> <Unknown>ROLLED</Unknown> <Unknown>NICE</Unknown> <Unknown>ARTWORK</Unknown> 
@<Unknown>JColeNC</Unknown> <Location>Forest Hills</Location> <Unknown>Drive</Unknown> <Unknown>Tour</Unknown>. <Unknown>Act</Unknown> 3 <Location>Hollywood</Location>. <Unknown>Featuring</Unknown> Big <Person>Sean</Person>. <Unknown>YG</Unknown>. <Unknown>Jeremih</Unknown>. http t.co J4fT33Z8dT
<Unknown>Queens</Unknown> Of The <Location>Stone</Location> <Unknown>Age</Unknown> No One <Unknown>Knows</Unknown> seguira <Unknown>Cranberries</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location>
Hi @teresaamejiaa <Unknown>Wanna</Unknown> get <Unknown>FREE</Unknown> 2000 stars on <Person>Kim K Hollywood</Person>? Check this <Unknown>SECRET</Unknown> trick <Unknown>LINK</Unknown> on my <Unknown>PROFILE</Unknown>
I m now a <Person>B List</Person> celebrity in <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location>. You can be famous too by playing on iPhone M http t.co 1<Unknown>WaM</Unknown>9jwfgn
<Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Free</Unknown> Games http t.co 6tiMWK9C0c  <Person>Kim  Hollywood</Person>  <Unknown>Game</Unknown>
@<Unknown>NerdPowersUnite</Unknown> @Lady9<Unknown>NewOrleans</Unknown> It s not a new thing though. <Location>Hollywood</Location> has long had a history of emasculating black men by having the
I m now an E List celebrity in <Person>Kim Kardashian</Person> <Location>Hollywood</Location>. You can be famous too by playing on iPhone http t.co c1kBIa8<Unknown>Kwe</Unknown>
First millions for <Organization>Hollywood Film TV</Organization> now proposed millions for music moguls. When is it struggling small biz turn? http t.co dTPK3<Unknown>BJlxV</Unknown>
<Unknown>Hey</Unknown> @ayeeitsbeccaa wanna get 6000 <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> for <Unknown>FREE</Unknown>? Check <Unknown>Detail</Unknown> <Unknown>Secrets</Unknown> on my <Unknown>Bio</Unknown> <Unknown>Profile</Unknown>
Hello @dollfacetrece Find out the <Unknown>Tricks</Unknown> to get 5000 <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> for <Unknown>FREE</Unknown>. Check <Unknown>Detail</Unknown> <Unknown>Secrets</Unknown> on my <Unknown>Bio</Unknown> <Unknown>Profile</Unknown>
<Unknown>Hey</Unknown> @hamilt4 <Unknown>Wanna</Unknown> get 5000 <Unknown>Stars</Unknown> <Unknown>Cash</Unknown> <Person>Kim Hollywood</Person> for <Unknown>FREE</Unknown>? Check <Unknown>Detail</Unknown> <Unknown>Secrets</Unknown> on my <Unknown>Bio</Unknown> <Unknown>Profile</Unknown>
What if I did an  <Unknown>Indiegogo</Unknown> to prepare my  kickstarter like a <Location>Hollywood</Location> movie trailer?  growthhacker
<Person>Movie</Person> <Unknown>Finance</Unknown> for <Location>Hollywood</Location>  <Unknown>TOMOOffMarket</Unknown> http t.co 50<Unknown>FSMAWwoc</Unknown>
@<Unknown>VanityFair</Unknown> <Unknown>Happy</Unknown> <Unknown>Birthday</Unknown> <Person>Steve McQueen</Person> the definition of <Location>Hollywood</Location> Cool http t.co 99kJHavvy4 http t.co 8<Unknown>ADeFi</Unknown>3crF
@<Unknown>Iam</Unknown>1izzo Big S O 2 @<Unknown>LeoDiCaprio</Unknown> for getting the young R B celebrities ready for  <Location>Hollywood</Location>  <Unknown>YoungHollywood</Unknown>  <Unknown>NextUp</Unknown>  <Unknown>Movies</Unknown> @etnow  <Unknown>TM</Unknown>
@<Unknown>TheAVClub</Unknown> You can watch the 1st ep of @<Unknown>ComedyCentral</Unknown> s new series Big <Unknown>Time</Unknown> In <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Location>FL</Location> right now http t.co 5<Unknown>JJwJpUWaY</Unknown> http 
<Unknown>ADeco</Unknown> <Unknown>Old</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Affair</Unknown> Wedding <Unknown>Decor</Unknown>. Love the flowers mixed with the pheasant feathers http t.co 13<Unknown>NBluCKXk</Unknown>
@<Unknown>ArkansasAuthors</Unknown> <Unknown>Meet</Unknown> @<Unknown>AceCollins</Unknown>  author of Man s Best <Person>Hero</Person> and <Person>Hollywood</Person> Lost http t.co <Unknown>JupR</Unknown>5tBR6q http t.co E63<Unknown>HHDo</Unknown>0<Unknown>Qp</Unknown>
<Location>Highway</Location> to <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Unknown>Trailer</Unknown> http t.co <Unknown>ZkCbVaRpeh</Unknown> via @<Unknown>YouTube</Unknown>
@<Unknown>GOPLdrBrianKolb</Unknown> First millions for <Organization>Hollywood Film TV</Organization> now proposed millions for music moguls. When is it struggling small biz turn? 
<Unknown>ATTI</Unknown>  <Unknown>ML</Unknown>04orange Bus 100 is at <Person>Sam</Person> s Club and is now turning to <Organization>Orange</Organization> South. Next <Unknown>Stopis</Unknown> <Location>Hollywood</Location> and <Unknown>Domain</Unknown> <Unknown>Apts</Unknown>. 3 24 2015 4 25 22 PM
From <Unknown>Monatana</Unknown> <Unknown>Ave</Unknown> to <Unknown>Main</Unknown> <Unknown>St</Unknown> @<Unknown>Beauticate</Unknown> shows how to do  <Unknown>SantaMonica</Unknown> <Unknown>Hollywoods</Unknown> cool beachy cousin right. http t.co q7E12<Unknown>UEMVi</Unknown>
I liked a @<Unknown>YouTube</Unknown> video from @kiss network http t.co o45<Unknown>UwS</Unknown>42h0 <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Person><Unknown>Traincase</Unknown> LOLA</Person> V
<Location>HOLLYWOOD</Location> <Unknown>THEATER</Unknown> <Unknown>ROW</Unknown> coming soon to <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Location>East Hollywood</Location> <Organization>Chamber of Commerce</Organization> http t.co 25Z3<Unknown>HVzia</Unknown>0
@<Unknown>TheAVClub</Unknown> You can watch the 1st ep of @<Unknown>ComedyCentral</Unknown> s new series Big <Unknown>Time</Unknown> In <Location>Hollywood</Location> <Location>FL</Location> right now http t.co 5<Unknown>JJwJpUWaY</Unknown> http 
@ <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> by <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> @<Unknown>Applebees</Unknown>  <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown>  <Unknown>Nature</Unknown>  <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> http t.co S2Y3<Unknown>DvCKBz</Unknown>
@archeteer @<Person>vic Pascual</Person>  photography  architecture <Location>Santiago</Location> <Location>Calatrava City</Location> of <Unknown>Arts</Unknown> and Sciences. <Location>Valencia</Location> <Location>Spain</Location> http t.co tFX5y
New post <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> books we love <Unknown>Understanding</Unknown> <Unknown>Exposure</Unknown> thirdedition http t.co YU3<Unknown>VfQMlex</Unknown>  itslikereally
Find out how to create <Unknown>AUTOUPDATED</Unknown> <Unknown>Blogger</Unknown> blogs here it s <Unknown>FREE</Unknown>. http t.co C4n9ygFb8d http t.co 1<Unknown>URSRYUswq</Unknown> 21 <Unknown>Stup</Unknown>...
@ <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> by <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> @<Unknown>Applebees</Unknown>  <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown>  <Unknown>Nature</Unknown>  <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> http t.co S2Y3<Unknown>DvCKBz</Unknown>
Top <Unknown>Secret</Unknown> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Unknown>Tutorials</Unknown> Enter Here.. and download <Unknown>Trick</Unknown> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> Special Effects 2nd http t.co p8p9yjxqOL  <Unknown>Libros</Unknown>
@monicatakvam CALL FOR <Unknown>ENTRIES</Unknown> <Unknown>Renaissance</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Unknown>Prize</Unknown> 2015 now open for submission  <Unknown>RPP</Unknown>2015 http t.co lYN4<Unknown>KFu</Unknown>1yc http t.c
Your About <Organization>Page Establishing Trust</Organization> http t.co o2xZIilJ42  photography  advice
@<Unknown>Network</Unknown> <Unknown>Easy</Unknown> <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Unknown>Qualasha</Unknown> 2 by mikeshoys  landscapes http t.co xVr6nYFdF3
<Unknown>Life</Unknown> is like photography. You need the negatives to develop.
Thank you @<Unknown>ExclusiveTailor</Unknown> for giving me K about <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> https t.co 0<Unknown>QmaMQARkM</Unknown>
@<Unknown>CutPics</Unknown> <Unknown>Microscopic</Unknown> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> http t.co xgG8<Unknown>DpcfaL</Unknown>
  56396 . Another product of the all nighter sunrise over a neighbouring roof in <Location>Leicester</Location>.  photography  sun http t.co C9bckqodK3
<Unknown>Thinking</Unknown> about buying <Location>UK</Location> <Location>Highland</Location> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown>? <Unknown>Read</Unknown> our latest review of the produ https t.co <Unknown>NUkfLCPmKn</Unknown> via @yotpo http t.co <Unknown>CkbdLMtOAV</Unknown>
@<Unknown>DWAWest</Unknown> <Unknown>Monochrome</Unknown> adventures 120  picoftheday  <Location>Newhaven</Location>  <Location>Sussex</Location>  photography  landscape  blackandwhite  <Organization>Leica</Organization> http t.co 3<Unknown>FxsEKZL</Unknown>6S
<Person>Susanne</Person> against white backdrop by <Person>Carl Hult</Person> https t.co <Unknown>UhfA</Unknown>9nXuTB  <Unknown>YouPic</Unknown>  photography  <Unknown>PIcSher</Unknown>  <Unknown>TeamCanon</Unknown>
<Unknown>GORILLA</Unknown> <Unknown>MONSOON</Unknown> <Unknown>LIVE</Unknown> by <Unknown>XIII</Unknown> <Unknown>PHOTOGRAPHY</Unknown> http t.co wulWEtyRv3
Love is sweet.  love  candy  photography ellahaus  wedding  candybar  vancouverwedding https t.co R6jgv7<Unknown>SJjC</Unknown>
@<Person><Unknown>OnePerfectShot</Unknown> LAWRENCE</Person> OF <Unknown>ARABIA</Unknown> 1962 Director of <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Person>Freddie Young</Person> Director <Person>David Lean</Person> http t.co <Unknown>OiOGgSj</Unknown>83q
@<Unknown>AnnieLyden</Unknown> Looking fwd to hearing <Person>Martin Barnes</Person> of @V and A talk about <Person>S African</Person> photo tomorrow @<Unknown>NatGalleriesSco</Unknown>.  <Unknown>NGSPonteCity</Unknown> https 
<Unknown>Springtime</Unknown> Fly. 
Our Director of <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Person>Bryan Pereira</Person> will be presenting to the <Organization>Scarborough Photographic Club Ontario</Organization> ... http t.co fKrKLTpr2F
@mainlygems So to all of you who think being a photography student is fucking easy I ll shove my expenses up your ass and hand u a cup
what classes do y all want for high school? I think I m gonna take choir photography idk what else
@ggwildlife225 in deep thought  <Unknown>WildLondoner</Unknown>  <Unknown>WWTLondon</Unknown>  <Location>London</Location>  <Unknown>Wildlife</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> http t.co pOmyI2cKVA
<Unknown>Done</Unknown> @<Unknown>MatHombauer</Unknown> join my brand new  conce photography  flickr  group here http t.co <Unknown>Hzi</Unknown>9<Unknown>UkRTt</Unknown>8
Just got book for a 300 photoshoot fuck a nigga mean  Active <Unknown>Photography</Unknown>
@<Unknown>RFWPPI</Unknown> 2015 wedding and portrait  photography conference expo reports growth in nearly every measure http t.co <Unknown>EuK</Unknown>8<Unknown>IhSr</Unknown>8t
The Growth Of <Unknown>Video</Unknown> And What It <Unknown>Means</Unknown> For Your <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Unknown>Business</Unknown>  <Unknown>Fstoppers</Unknown> https t.co bOUCqctV2d
<Unknown>Awesome</Unknown> Examples Of <Unknown>Fashion</Unknown> <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> 19 images http t.co <Unknown>MBmLr</Unknown>7ly1E
 <Unknown>Distinguishing</Unknown> Your <Person>Brand</Person> In A <Unknown>Saturated</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> <Unknown>Market</Unknown> <Unknown>Tips</Unknown> For A... http t.co <Unknown>Pd</Unknown>2tw4fBhD http t.co rS39h9c1<Unknown>Yn</Unknown>
@<Unknown>DWAWest</Unknown> <Unknown>Monochrome</Unknown> adventures 120  picoftheday  <Location>Newhaven</Location>  <Location>Sussex</Location>  photography  landscape  blackandwhite  <Organization>Leica</Organization> http t.co 3<Unknown>FxsEKZL</Unknown>6S
@<Unknown>RFWPPI</Unknown> 2015 wedding and portrait  photography conference expo reports growth in nearly every measure http t.co <Unknown>UuA</Unknown>22bGanK
http t.co lnhCcrtrnw http t.co dhG8y2<Unknown>KfKk</Unknown> photography http t.co 5<Unknown>JHmjGty</Unknown>2b
I just added P41 <Unknown>Eisbrecher</Unknown> to The Director of <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> https t.co <Unknown>MWVdnsp</Unknown>1FO
@jasonburrows  <Unknown>Landscape</Unknown> on 500px <Location>Loon Island</Location> <Unknown>Lighthouse</Unknown> by miketaylorphoto 
 photography  photoofthed http t.co 3yqEq8sJan http 
How to master the aof flower photography <Unknown>Mother</Unknown> <Unknown>Nature</Unknown> <Unknown>Network</Unknown> blog http t.co <Unknown>QUqJNMMtVe</Unknown>
Viewpoint and <Unknown>Angles</Unknown> in <Unknown>Photography</Unknown> http t.co s1<Unknown>UO</Unknown>7Y8<Unknown>Jha</Unknown>
Good advice https t.co <Unknown>OQSExrRGKD</Unknown>  photography... http t.co <Unknown>YTTDoQ</Unknown>6j1J
Last night photo shoot.
 kapchur  photography  natural  canon  freelance  photos  videography https t.co tdMPD6<Unknown>GOk</Unknown>1
@ <Unknown>Akanshagautam</Unknown> <Unknown>Meanders</Unknown> by <Person>Mike Reyfman</Person> @<Unknown>Applebees</Unknown>  <Unknown>Landscapes</Unknown>  <Unknown>Photography</Unknown>  <Unknown>Nature</Unknown>  <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> http t.co S2Y3<Unknown>DvCKBz</Unknown>
A1 It may not be happening during  <Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown> we re excited about the Responsible <Organization>Tourism</Organization> conf in CT http t.co <Unknown>ODdRMEEIPG</Unknown>  <Unknown>EHchat</Unknown>
@<Unknown>WalesAirForum</Unknown> <Person>Roger Lewis</Person> confirmed as next <Location>Cardiff</Location> <Unknown>Airpochairman</Unknown> http t.co <Unknown>FCUhP</Unknown>0drq8  <Location>Cardiff</Location>  <Location>Wales</Location>  avgeek  <Unknown>WalestotheWorld</Unknown>  
@tibettruth So you want to  travel to  trueTibet?  tourism contributing to  erosion of  <Unknown>Tibetan</Unknown> culture http t.co b0oC2<Unknown>Issuq</Unknown>
@tibettruth  trueTibet a sacred landscape turned into a  tourist theme park by <Location>China</Location> s terrorist regime  travel  tourism http t.co F
<Unknown>Astronomical</Unknown> <Organization>Tourism</Organization> in the country with the best skies for astronomical observation worldwide  ast http t.co sbvO6<Unknown>VUCE</Unknown>0
@tibettruth  trueTibet a sacred landscape turned into a  tourist theme park by <Location>China</Location> s terrorist regime  travel  tourism http t.co F
@<Unknown>CatalanMuseums</Unknown> Sadly some of <Organization>Catalan Museum</Organization> souvenirs are still related with a wrong idea of tourism. Our visitors are clever. Don t f
.@<Unknown>Traveller</Unknown>24 SA Sounds interesting. <Organization>Tourism</Organization> has an important role to play in our global sustainability  <Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown>  <Unknown>EHchat</Unknown>
@hany2m <Unknown>Inbound</Unknown> tourism to  <Location>Egypt</Location> increases by 5.5 pct in <Person>Jan CAPMAS</Person> http t.co gxr46<Unknown>SFykb</Unknown>
A photographic tour through the recent Skills <Unknown>Development</Unknown> <Unknown>Programme</Unknown> conducted at the <Unknown>Wakkerstroom</Unknown> <Organization>Tourism</Organization> and... http t.co knAM9<Unknown>SBISf</Unknown>
 <Unknown>Turismo</Unknown>  <Unknown>Zaia</Unknown> presenta <Unknown>SmaGuide</Unknown> <Organization>Tourism</Organization> <Person>al  Vinitaly</Person> http t.co 23fj8<Unknown>ESlb</Unknown>9
@<Unknown>WWFSouthAfrica</Unknown> .@<Unknown>Traveller</Unknown>24 SA Sounds interesting. <Organization>Tourism</Organization> has an important role to play in our global sustainability  <Unknown>EarthHourSA</Unknown>  E
@geckobike the whole idea of  tourism to  <Location>Tibet</Location> in any form is deeply toubling in terms of ethics
@<Location>Iran</Location>  <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> Making trips to  <Location>Shiraz</Location>  <Unknown>Hafezieh</Unknown> on  <Unknown>Nowruz</Unknown> holidays
 <Organization>Tourism</Organization>  <Location>Iran</Location>  <Unknown>MustSeeIran</Unknown> http t.co U
Morning ijen <Unknown>Crater</Unknown> <Location>East Java</Location> <Location>Indonesia</Location>  tourism eastjava holiday kids <Location>Indonesia</Location> https t.co r1ikfMU4<Unknown>Xb</Unknown>
<Location>Atlantic City</Location> s newest tourism push touts entertainment http t.co m8<Unknown>NFNrePUm</Unknown>
 ac  atlantic  <Location>jersey</Location>
<Unknown>Attending</Unknown> <Organization>HM</Organization> visit to @<Unknown>RoyalMuseumJo</Unknown> supporting  <Organization>Tourism</Organization> in  <Location>Jordan</Location>  <Unknown>ShareYourJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown>  <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> http t.co ld6<Unknown>MKiXwat</Unknown>
Off to  <Location>Manchester</Location> for the day  tourism  sightseeing
@<Unknown>AnasAlShariff</Unknown> <Unknown>Attending</Unknown> <Organization>HM</Organization> visit to @<Unknown>RoyalMuseumJo</Unknown> supporting  <Organization>Tourism</Organization> in  <Location>Jordan</Location>  <Unknown>ShareYourJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown>  <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> http
Regional tourism survey predicts continued growth and new jobs in tourism sector It is regarded by many busin... http t.co d53<Unknown>XjDcXbH</Unknown>
@<Person>meta</Person> guide lc <Location>St. Lucia</Location> <Unknown>Continues</Unknown> <Unknown>Record</Unknown> Breaking <Organization>Tourism</Organization> <Unknown>Growth</Unknown> in 2015 http t.co hEMdEXbK4M
@<Unknown>AnasAlShariff</Unknown> <Unknown>Attending</Unknown> <Organization>HM</Organization> visit to @<Unknown>RoyalMuseumJo</Unknown> supporting  <Organization>Tourism</Organization> in  <Location>Jordan</Location>  <Unknown>ShareYourJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>LoveJO</Unknown>  <Unknown>GoJordan</Unknown>  <Unknown>VisitJordan</Unknown> http
My taxi driver just described <Unknown>Artane</Unknown> as Not that horrible of a place. Get that guy a job on the tourism board now.
Best Places To <Unknown>Visit</Unknown> in The <Location>United States</Location> http t.co bVOf3<Unknown>KCqgK</Unknown> 
@th3programe Best Places To <Unknown>Visit</Unknown> in The <Location>United States</Location> http t.co bVOf3<Unknown>KCqgK</Unknown> 
@njerudeee <Unknown>Security</Unknown> fears in <Location>Kenya</Location> have inadvertently worked in <Unknown>Tanzanias</Unknown> favor as far as tourism goes but now secure safe http t
<Unknown>THIS</Unknown> IS THE <Unknown>BEST</Unknown> <Organization>TOURISM</Organization> <Unknown>WEBSITE</Unknown> I <Unknown>HAVE</Unknown> <Unknown>EVER</Unknown> <Unknown>SEEN</Unknown>
<Unknown>Dmitris</Unknown> <Unknown>Tsoukalas</Unknown> from  iamanathenian is a private company to promote tourism in <Location>Athens</Location> and <Location>Greece</Location>  <Unknown>SoMeT</Unknown>15EU http t.co <Unknown>PIUG</Unknown>2v0Uzi
instanusantara challenge. repost old photo. explore <Location>indonesia</Location> tourism to the world. Street in <Unknown>Gunung</Unknown> https t.co <Unknown>ZODGYznjyO</Unknown>
<Location>London</Location> Mayor <Person>Boris Johnson</Person> to boost tourism with hidden gems of <Location>London</Location> ... <Unknown>Evening</Unknown> <Unknown>Standard</Unknown> http t.co 2xQin0<Unknown>Tho</Unknown>2
<Unknown>CCCU</Unknown> hospitality and tourism are here too with pick your best logo comp  logoideas   kentchoices http t.co a5fptYVYgQ
@<Unknown>EstherPassaris</Unknown> @<Organization>AMB</Organization> A <Person>Mohammed</Person> well said dear our tourism sector is amng our pride let s bring nd show out what essens nature beauty we hav
Japanese hot spring <Unknown>Kurokawa</Unknown> <Unknown>Onsen</Unknown> introduction <Location>Tokyo</Location> Olympics <Location>Japan</Location> <Organization>Tourism</Organization> <Unknown>Video</Unknown> http t.co qEpPDIu5AY  Olympics
@th3programe Best Places To <Unknown>Visit</Unknown> in The <Location>United States</Location> http t.co bVOf3<Unknown>KCqgK</Unknown> 
@masterclassing Save a seat at our <Unknown>Digital</Unknown> <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> and <Organization>Tourism</Organization> <Unknown>Masterclass</Unknown> in <Location>Dubai</Location> on April 15th here http t.co uA8eH1<Unknown>Wqig</Unknown>
<Location>North East</Location> is really good. Gov. should promote tourism.
@masterclassing How can <Unknown>Travel</Unknown> and <Organization>Tourism</Organization> brands build engaging relationships with their social audience ? @<Unknown>Brandwatch</Unknown> http t.co <Unknown>Pj</Unknown>
@th3programe Best Places To <Unknown>Visit</Unknown> in The <Location>United States</Location> http t.co bVOf3<Unknown>KCqgK</Unknown> 
@<Location>Iran</Location>  <Unknown>Photos</Unknown> Making trips to  <Location>Shiraz</Location>  <Unknown>Hafezieh</Unknown> on  <Unknown>Nowruz</Unknown> holidays
 <Organization>Tourism</Organization>  <Location>Iran</Location>  <Unknown>MustSeeIran</Unknown> http t.co U
@<Unknown>Post</Unknown> <Location>Nigeria</Location> <Unknown>FG</Unknown> to curb medical tourism with 6 referral hospitals <Unknown>Post</Unknown> <Location>Nigeria</Location> http t.co <Unknown>Bxnbm</Unknown>6<Unknown>TI</Unknown>1g
@<Unknown>BittuSahgal</Unknown> <Location>Rwanda</Location> learned how to turn tourism to advantage while helping communities. <Location>India</Location> should take a leaf out of that book http
 @<Unknown>Post</Unknown> <Location>Nigeria</Location> <Unknown>FG</Unknown> to curb medical tourism with 6 referral hospitals <Unknown>Post</Unknown> <Location>Nigeria</Location> http t.co <Unknown>YPAIajvteW</Unknown>  <Unknown>WeTriumphStill</Unknown>  <Unknown>IchooseGEJ</Unknown>
Our <Unknown>Head</Unknown> of School of <Organization>Hospitality Management</Organization> and <Organization>Tourism</Organization> writes about the future of tourism in <Location>Ireland</Location> in the... http t.co pIADv8wMKS
@oleebranch <Unknown>Kyaninga</Unknown> <Unknown>Triathlon</Unknown> The <Unknown>Mighty</Unknown> <Unknown>Rim</Unknown> http t.co fCiR0u9<Unknown>Ucw</Unknown>  <Unknown>UGblogs</Unknown>  256<Unknown>Blogs</Unknown>  <Unknown>VisitUganda</Unknown>  <Unknown>Triathlon</Unknown>  <Unknown>Fitness</Unknown>  <Unknown>Fitfam</Unknown>  <Unknown>Ad</Unknown>
<Unknown>Humber</Unknown> <Location>East Liberal</Location> @stelmanflynnMHA is in studio to talk about businesses excluded from a provincial tourism guide. http t.co <Unknown>YocziqhF</Unknown>6v
<Organization>Tourism</Organization> in <Location>Barcelona</Location> http t.co B6vvmzkehO </paragraph>
